Hey.
>> Waheguru Ji Ka Khalsa and Waheguru Ji Ka
Fateh.
Um, and good morning, good evening,
wherever you are, ladies and gentlemen.
Today, um, I am here with a very, very
special, uh, broadcast or live stream
on, um, a breaking news.
Um, a really high-end revelation by an
very high-ranking ex-CIA official, which
has really set the geo not just, um, the
overall Twitter stream, um, discussion
on Twitter alive, but has also, uh, set
off many, uh, you know, deep-seated,
uh, long issues which have been pending
resolution and have brought them to
fore.
Today, we are going to discuss the
latest revelations by an ex-CIA
official, a very high-ranking official,
whose name is John Kiriakou,
regarding India's hand in Air India 182
bombing.
Air India 182 was a flight which
actually was bombed in 1985,
in which 329
innocent
civilians had died, 82 of them children,
and 268 out of them Canadian citizens.
Before 9/11, this was the biggest
incident of aviation terrorism in human
history.
From the time that this incident
happened, there have been so many
questions.
There have been court cases, inquiries,
but in all the court cases, almost all
the major accused got scot-free. There
were sham public inquiries by the
Canadian establishment which had some
terms of reference which never allowed
it to fix responsibility for the bombing
in spite of so much of evidence being
available about the people who were
involved in the bombing.
We've had
trail of money that has been tracked
publicly with all the evidence available
to the main financer of this particular
terror act which was traced to the
Indian government. We've had
CSIS investigators, the Canadian
intelligence investigators who actually
investigated this particular act of
terrorism
whistleblow and share information that
they had full evidence that Indian state
was involved or Indian agencies were
involved in this act of terror. However,
they had to suppress all that evidence
because of the Canadian politicians
deciding to give more priority to good
trade relations with India versus
letting the public know the truth. We've
had
unending number of witnesses, five to
six first-hand witnesses who came to the
court case and shared evidence against
the main accused in the bombing, but all
of them, in spite of that evidence, were
let go off free except one person who
was given a very light sentence for
killing.
We've had not just the CSIS
investigators, but also 22 congressmen
from US Congress actually signed a
letter to US government
in year 2000 asking for India to be
sanctioned as a state sponsor of terror
for the bombing that it conducted of
this flight.
However, in spite of all this evidence,
we've never the public discourse has or
the public spotlight was never put on to
this dastardly act and who the main
conspirators were. Even today, the main
conspirators live we don't know, maybe
some of them are not living, but they
are scot-free. Justice has still not
been done.
But, in this long stream of evidence
which has been building up about the
hand of the Indian state in this
dastardly terror act, we now have
one new nail in that coffin.
And that nail comes from nobody else.
It doesn't come from a average Tom,
Dick, and Harry, average person like me.
It comes from none other than one of the
higher ranking ex-CIA
officials. His name is John Kiriakou.
Recently, last week,
while giving an interview to Chris
Hedges, Chris Hedges is another Pulitzer
Award-winning journalist, John revealed
what was already an open secret, which
is kind of an open talk in the
intelligent circles, which is that the
Indian agencies blew up this Boeing 747
in 1985
named as Kanishka.
And that bombing was engineered by the
Indian agencies
reportedly to defame and delegitimize
the Sikh freedom struggle called
Khalistan.
So, today we are going to go through the
these latest revelations and I will not
only walk you through these revelations,
I'll also walk you through some of the
other evidence that we have.
So, without further ado, let us listen
to what John Kiriakou had to say.
And I'm going to play his video
off for you guys.
Okay. So, this was the interview he gave
to Chris Hedges, and there are twice he
brings up the name of the the the case
of Kanishka or Air India 182 bombing.
This is the first time that he talks
about it. Let me play the video.
that carried out acts of terrorism
against its own people.
Look at Israel that has carried out
assassinations all over the world.
Or we could even point the finger at the
at the government of India for that
matter, for carrying out assassinations
and terrorist attacks in Canada, blowing
up a 747,
no less.
So, really the complaint that I have
with this designation, this terrorism
designation
Let me play that out again. Again.
That's a great example, but but look at
others. Look at the let's say the Greek
military junta, for example, that
carried out acts of terrorism against
its own people.
Look at Israel that has carried out
assassinations all over the world.
Or we could even point the finger at the
at the government of India for that
matter, for carrying out assassinations
and terrorist attacks in Canada, blowing
up a 747,
no less.
So, really the complaint that I have
Amazing. Amazing.
So, so this is John Kiriakou alleging
that Indian were
behind the Air India 182 bombing.
The blowing up the 747 jet in Canada on
the Canadian soil, killing total 329
innocent people. 82 of them children
and 268 out of them Canadian citizens.
And it's kind of quite like it's amazing
how he how he talks about it because in
this interview he talks about Israel
having committed crimes. He talks about
Greek military junta junta and then in
that mix he puts in India right up
there.
And and if you if you kind of understand
a bit of body language, you have to see
when he talks about India. He has this
indignation when he says India.
And then when he talks about blowing up
aircraft in Canada, look at the way his
eyes lit up and the way he's surprised
that how can how come this happened? How
come this third world country come to a
western country and blow up a plane and
get away with it? Let me play this out
again for you if you are watching on the
watching it on the
um
on the video that I have. Just play this
out again. See how he how he actually
reacts when he talks about this terror
act by Indian state. Greek military
junta, for example, that carried out
acts of terrorism against its own
people.
Look at Israel that has carried out
assassinations all over the world.
Uh we could even point the finger at the
at the government of India for that
matter for carrying out assassinations
and terrorist attacks in Canada, blowing
up a 747
no less. No less.
A 747 no less.
Let me just uh and this is now almost
kind of more than halfway through the
interview. He brings up India again
without any
hint or any
kind of prompt from the interviewer.
He basically brings up India again on
his own and let me play that play this
out for you guys.
This is the second time he talks about
India in the interview.
Uh very poor planning. We could say the
same thing about the Indians.
In that, you know, the Indians support
their own Kashmiri
separatist groups, extremist groups.
And
and it's the Indians that blew up the
747 in Canada. It's the Indians that
carry out hits or attempted hits against
Sikh activists or or Indian leftists or
anti-Hindu nationalists in places like
Canada or the UK. There's plenty of
blame to go around.
Amazing. Let me let me play that again
for you when he talks about And here
he's accusing India of not just
Air India
182 bombing. He is accusing India of
other murders that have recently been in
the news in UK and in Canada. And he
also talks about the attempted hits in
US for which we have a couple of
Indian terrorists currently in US
custody in New York.
So, let's talk about that again. And
it's the Indians that blew up the 747 in
Canada. It's the Indians that carry out
hits or attempted hits against Sikh
activists or or Indian leftists or
anti-Hindu nationalists in places like
Canada or the UK. There's plenty of
blame to go around. And and not to even
begin to discuss what the CIA does on a
daily basis.
Okay. Now, one thing I really find
interesting is he he lays very very
specific allegations against India, but
he talks about other agencies as well.
But like in there, he doesn't lay out
any specific allegation. There's no
specific allegation against CIA. He
said, "Oh, CIA does this. Uh he does you
know, Mossad does this. Assassination.
Blah blah blah." But like, he never laid
out any particular incident like being
very specific. Then he talks about Greek
military junta and other dictators and
all doing it. But in case of India, he
goes very very specific. So, I find it
very interesting. And another thing I
noticed is like how when he talks about
this, he talks about it as if like this
is just common knowledge. Like nobody
should be surprised.
Like nobody in in my world, that's what
he's saying, nobody in my world in the
intelligence world is surprised. Hey,
it's India. They've carried out the 747.
We know it. We knew it all along.
And and that is exactly and he's totally
right. I totally agree with him because
he is not the only one saying it. If he
was a lone guy saying it, we would have
said maybe he's gone mad.
But we have
two confirmed CSIS investigators who
have said this. And I'll walk you
through that evidence.
We have one CSIS
Asia Pacific Bureau Chief who has
written
so in a book in a published book, Nest
of Spies, that Indians were behind it.
We have court evidence wherein we have
all the the main accused, the financier,
having all his money being taken from
the Indian government
through a millions of dollars of loan
that he got from the Indian government.
And then we have a sham public inquiry
which we know was given terms of
reference that you are not going to
investigate any government of India.
You're not going to fix responsibility
for the bombing.
And then we have also
the main accused, the financier of this
entire operation, having deep linkages
with India, having been welcomed by the
Indian government, treated, given a red
carpet. Unfortunately, unfortunately,
he's been murdered. And we'll talk about
it, but let's talk about some of the
other people. He's not the lone only
one. We have other people saying the
same stuff.
So, let me pull up
some of the other claims on this.
Okay, here you go.
Here is this book
by the CSIS bureau chief.
And I'm going to just read verbatim from
it, okay? This Nest of Spies. I think
this was published around 2004. Yuno
Katsuwon.
And this is what he says. He has a full
one chapter devoted to Air India 182.
And I quote,
"Flight 182 isn't just a tragedy. It is
also a Pandora's Box with a Latin weight
of Canada's entire governmental
apparatus still sitting on the lid and
trying to keep it shut."
"Concealed inside, apart from the
murderers, is the dark history of India
itself
in the form of steely-eyed agents bent
on settling New Delhi's accounts and
prepared to cross anybody's borders in
order to do so."
"How would Canadians feel if it were
known that India's agents provocateurs
had pulled just one tiny thread in
making this disaster come about?
Or at best had known that it was going
to happen and chosen to stand aside."
"What might Canadians do if they do
discover if they discover that our
authorities had tolerated foreign
interference that was bound to spill
quantities of blood for no other reason
than to ensure the continued prosperity
of corporate interests and the
untroubled afternoon teas of our
diplomats."
I think he's spot-on when he kind of
characterizes this
incident because we know through this is
some of the paper cutting that you're
currently seeing. These are the news
reports that immediately came out after
the bombing wherein CSIS and RCMP was
leaking all the, you know, information
they had about the Indian hand and their
suspects being primarily the Indian
Consulate.
Here is an excerpt, you know, from the
great investigative work that was done
by two
two, I would say, very credible
journalists, one from Global and Mail,
another from
uh Toronto Star. And their account was
based upon the disclosures by two CSIS
investigators who were actually involved
in the investigation of this bombing.
And I quote from the book, quote, "So
convinced had CSIS become of the
Government of India connection that at
one Air India task force meeting a CSIS
agent had seriously suggested that if
you really want to clear the incidents
quickly, take vans down to the Indian
High Commission and the consulates in
Toronto and Vancouver, load up everybody
and take them down for questioning. We
know it and they know it that they are
involved."
Not just that, in this particular book,
they actually laid out the entire
conspiracy. This book was published in
1988 where they laid out that the main
financer was Ripudaman Singh Malik,
quote unquote plant of India, who was
given $2 million worth of credit line by
the Indian government through its bank
in Vancouver City. And that particular
person was the main financer of these
extremist element or what I call foot
soldiers who were then trying to put a
bomb-laden baggage on the aircraft.
All these the all these people were
named, Mr. Bagri, Reyat, Ripudaman Singh
Malik in 1988 itself in a book, a public
book.
But CSIS and RCMP slept for 16 years.
They did nothing. Then year 2000,
suddenly they wake up and they have to
charge all these people who are named in
this book. And they have to charge not
because of some great investigative
work, but they have to charge because
there are witnesses who came out on
their own.
the prime witness being the girlfriend
of Ripudaman Malik, the Indian implant
himself, who actually came to CC herself
as she could no longer answer her
consciousness and she revealed that hey,
in moments of weakness this person
Ripudaman Malik confessed to me what his
role was in this entire bombing
operation. That he was the one who
prepared these suitcases and hired these
people to put these bags on this
aircraft.
And not just her, we had two other
witnesses, Mr. A, Mr. B, who actually
witnessed, gave witness in the court
first hand that Ripudaman Malik himself
came and told them to put these
bomb-laden baggages on the aircraft.
But Ripudaman Malik goes scot-free.
Four accused people are accused in that
case, all goes scot-free except one guy.
One guy who is given five years in the
main trial for manslaughter, but in a
related trial 10 years, so let's say 15
years for manslaughter, which is not
part in being part of the conspiracy,
which basically is unintentional
killing. That he prepared some equipment
or bought some equipment which was
eventually used in the bombs.
So we never knew who the main
conspirators were. All of these guys
walked free.
We never knew we were told we will never
knew because the CC agents already told
us in their book that the the Canadian
government has already done a deal with
the Indians that they are not going to
name the Indian government. That they
are going to bury their head and they
don't want to destroy the diplomatic
relations, they don't want to destroy
the trade relations between India and
Canada. Money is way, way more important
than the blood of the innocents. So what
if the Indian government in its
foolishness, you know, did one act of
terrorism?
So the Canadian government fired six
diplomats of India in 1986 and that's
it.
That was And then when the families
cried for justice, people cried for
justice, and the witnesses themselves
came out, they ran a trial, all the
evidence was there, but then the judge,
after all the evidence was presented,
first-hand witnesses, the judge very
conveniently dismissed everything as
undeniable, not worth of, you know,
uh you know, uh
not kind of conclusive enough, and
everybody walked free, except one guy
for manslaughter.
And then, under pressure from the
public, the Canadian government
installed a inquiry.
Inquiry. People were given a false
impression that this public inquiry will
be something like a truth commission
where all the information will be
shared, but no, it was a clever ploy.
That inquiry had actually forbidden the
commissioner from fixing responsibility
for the bombing. He was specifically
forbidden from going into any evidence
of any foreign government involvement,
especially the Indian government
involvement. He was only to look after
things like airport security, lack of
coordination between RCMP and CSIS, and,
you know, uh what can we do better in
terms of security coordination between
our agencies, blah blah blah, but
nothing about the conspiracy or who is
responsible for the bombing. The excuse
that the government gave for these kind
of terms of reference were They said,
"We didn't want to jeopardize our
chances of litigation because this might
go to We might Investigation is still
open. We might go to trial tomorrow, so
we didn't already some accused got off,
so we didn't want to jeopardize chances
of future litigation."
That was the excuse given to to give
these kind of for very restrictive terms
of reference.
So, on paper, the RCMP still has this
investigation, I call, open, but the
reality is that they are not running it.
It is already buried. RCMP cannot
investigate a hostile act by a foreign
actor.
CSIS has that all that intelligence.
It is a political element which has to
let go, but the political element is
already compromised. They have already
agreed with India to abide their hand
and this is exactly what today John
Kiryakou exposed.
John Kiryakou today came on
on a YouTube social media channel and
exposed the fact that we know in the
intelligence circles who was behind this
which are the Indians.
The Indians blew this plane up. Let's
play it play it out again and and I have
certain listeners here very interesting
listeners. I I see Marshall here. I
don't know Marshall if you're going to
take speakers.
But uh feel free to take speaker.
My
I'm almost at the end of my main speech.
I would love to kind of get more views
on what people think
about these latest revelations.
And I'm sending you guys speaker.
But uh what is the what is really
important is like what people need to
understand is that why did Indian
government do it? Like some of you might
have this question like why did the
Indian government blew up a 747? What
what would they gain? They gained a lot
because in 1984 the Indian government at
um conducted a genocide of the Sikh
minority. Sikhs uh who are 2% of the
Indian population but are sizable uh
fifth largest religion in the world um
you know were were demanding some
political rights within the Indian setup
which the Indian government didn't want
to give. So it ended up conducting a um
a military operation against their
holiest place of worship called the
Barsana in Amritsar and then also
conducted a genocide of 35,000 innocent
Sikhs on the streets of national capital
of India and across 119 other cities. So
they were that had caused you know the
Sikhs
um in India as well as in diaspora to
rally together for a cause of separatism
for to get separate from India and have
an independent state. And that movement
was called Khalistan movement and it got
a lot of sympathy across around the
world. And so the Indian state and
Indian agency were under a lot of
pressure and what better way to come out
of that pressure than actually conduct a
terror attack and then blame the Sikhs
for it. And that's what they did.
They got in touch with their Canadian
friends and said, "Hey, we just want to
go and bomb this one particular
aircraft. Would you mind looking the
other way?"
And and I don't know whether they looked
the other way at the time of planning,
but they definitely looked the other way
the Canadian intelligence after the
bombing was done, even after knowing
that the Indians are behind it. So, the
Indians blew up this plane and then
overnight the whole story the world over
was changed. The Sikhs from being
victims of state terrorism were now
portrayed as these extremist religious
fanatics who are out for the blood of
the innocents.
And the Indian government flipped that
story and overnight they used this
particular incident to label an entire
community as fanatic, as extremist.
They killed their own people to create
this kind of an impression
and then blamed their own people,
another group of people under their own
rule as the ones who are fanatic and
extremist. An entire community, an
entire religion, millions of people were
blamed. I have met many Canadians uh
diaspora Sikhs who were young at that
point in time. They were in schools.
They got this stigma against their name
called a terrorist.
People have called me up and shared the
experiences of what experience they had
growing up as a young Sikh
in Canadian schools post this particular
terror attack.
People would call them terrorist
right there in their face.
A whole community defamed for what? For
nothing. For basically demanding their
own rights. And the people who did the
act are the ones who are doing the
blaming.
But as they say, you know, the truth is
hard to hard to hide.
Um the the mountain of evidence from
whistleblowers, from court documents,
from leaks,
from
conscientious objectors or
whistleblowers like John Kiriakou is
mounting up.
This is in the level of evidence that we
have now, which questions and clearly
points at the hand of the Indian
government,
deserves an answer.
The Canadian government will not be able
to escape for too long.
Very soon,
a mainstream media outlet will pick up
the story.
This story will be picked up.
And I say the ghost of Air India 182
won't die, won't go away until the
public is told the full truth.
Okay, with that, um, I have Max Steel,
whose hand is up. Max Steel, how are
you? Welcome to Khalsa Vibhuti
Uh, haan ji, paaji, Vibhuti Khalsa
Vibhuti Khalsa
Um, haan ji, haan ji, paaji, yeah, I
mean, it's a good thing that well,
right, that this this is come out, but I
think, um, uh,
the Canadian government is doing the
repeating the same story all over again,
like they killed her, uh, Hardeep Singh
Nijjar, right? And the Canadian
government, they went ahead and buried
it again, buried it again.
I think this is the modus operandi. This
is just how
the basically this Canadian state is in
is hands in glove with India. And, uh,
even with this Air India bombing, they
actually probably knew beforehand that
this was going to happen.
Uh, and they just let it happen.
So, um, I I personally I don't know
what's I mean,
what's going to come of it or how far
this is going to go,
because, uh, the this Canadian
government, they're hell-bent on burying
it and just, uh, move forward with their
so-called relationship with India.
Um,
and I mean, it's a good thing it's
coming I mean, I think the the reason
what
it's more credible is because it's
coming from a CIA agent.
Uh if it was coming out of a Canadian
resource or a
security member
intelligence member, it would not have
been as credible as credible as it is
now.
But I think you have to we're just going
to have to wait to see, right? How far
this goes because
uh Canada's going to do whatever they
can to parade and
uh
just going to
like cover it cover it up with
misinformation.
Yeah, Max, I kind of agree with you and
it's very unfortunate I I see it. But um
I was honestly, like when I was
investigating this, I I started reading
the court documents and and the um the
commission reports and
uh all the incidents that happened prior
to the bombing, it was clear to me that
the Canadian elements in Canadian
government
definitely knew about what's going on.
I was not actually and I'll I'll
I'll claim like I'm guilty of it. I
didn't talk about that evidence much
because in my heart I thought that that
can't be true. Like the Canadian
government can't be looking the other
way when they were planning. Maybe they
messed up
post the event. But honestly, if you if
you look at the
testimony from uh
Mr. Bartleman. I think I've forgotten
his first name.
He he's on record that he had conclusive
evidence before the bombing that this is
going to happen. And he went with that
piece of evidence, that wiretap of some
consulate's Indian India's consulate, to
the RCMP officer in charge of the ops
room on that day.
And he was basically told to shut up and
run away.
And when he gave the testimony in
commission,
the basically the Canadian government
went after him saying he's lying. And
Mr. Bartleman is not an ordinary guy. I
think he rose to be a premier of a
state.
And so so there's there's all this um
kind of I think the
Yeah, but I but I don't and you're right
I think we shouldn't expect anything out
of the Canadian government. They they
are now stuck in this. They they have
done the deal with the devil.
And but I hope for for the sake of
Canada.
Like how does Canada recover from this?
Like the Indian state indulge in that
terror attack and now it is killing
citizens what of Canada we we have
I think Kiriyako now basically say that
the Indians were involved behind the
murder of Sardar Hardeep Singh Nijjar
which is now a publicly known fact like
nobody even questions that.
And and the look we have the Prime
Minister of Canada doing trade deals
with India after that and then kind of
just
telling his own people oh no no we are
so poor Canadians we are so poor.
So what?
If a brown Canadian have been killed it
is some kind of a foreign dispute. We
can keep that on the side and we can
deal with the Indian and they'll be nice
with us and now suddenly we'll have
rivers of dollars coming our way. That's
the kind of I don't know like it it's
just it's just beyond me like what's
going on with Canada but sorry Marshall
go ahead.
Thanks for coming and joining Marshall
but
I don't know how you feel about it like
as I am an immigrant American a Sikh
immigrant to America
Max is probably an immigrant Sikh to
Canada but I don't know how you feel
about it once you know all this story
a white Canadian probably born in Canada
like how do you feel like what's going
on?
But it's crazy right? It's exactly what
what Max said. It's
the Canadian government knows about this
has always known about it. I said it to
you Hardeep too in our conversations.
It's there's no doubt the Canadian
government knew about this in the
beginning. I think I I you're right and
about it before
and it actually went down and they kind
of let it happen. I don't see how
anybody looking at all the evidence
can conclude anything else at all
and
you know, it was it was something else
to hear John Kiriakou just drop that
casually just casually drop that as if
it was common knowledge.
You know, and the guy he's known for
telling the truth. That's what he gets
in trouble for not for lying. He gets in
trouble for telling the truth. So he
just drops what he knows casually but
you know, everybody knows it. So as a
Canadian citizen it bothered me cuz and
it's not just India, right? It's the
last few years it's become clearer and
clearer. We're in bed with China. We're
in bed with Iran. We got terrorists
running all over the place. We got, you
know, communist Chinese running police
stations here.
Apparently, you know, they've taken over
entire ridings where nobody can elect
anybody without it being a
you know, a CCP at least a cheese and
you know, we none of us think it's a
cheese.
We all think they're a CCP at this
point.
So
you know, India was kind of the first
our government's and it's not just the
liberals it's the conservatives as well.
It's that is that is also clear. They
have their hand in covering up Air
India. They had their hand in covering
up
China. You know, and they make a big
deal about it now but who who can trust
them? That if they get elected instead
of the liberals that they're going to
come in and do something about it. I
don't think they will. I don't think
anything's ever going to be done about
Air India. I think the entire Canadian
political landscape needs to be totally
disrupted. It needs this this filth
that's going on for years now. It needs
to stop and it's
I I agree with what you say. I try not
to be too superstitious or whatever
about it but the ghosts of Air India are
not going to go away until there is some
justice.
And it's it's time for that justice to
come out. It's not going to happen in
our current political system. We're just
Something's wrong with this country.
Maybe we need the outside money that
badly.
But our governments, our political
parties are uninterested uninterested in
doing the right thing. That's what I
think about it.
Yeah, no, absolutely. And I just thought
I think it's just it's probably has to
come from outside and and um
I don't know what Well, let's talk
technically about this interview like
the way
I have listened to this whole interview
of John, but also for audiences who
don't know John. John is um
ex-CIA official on papers. He served God
knows how much he's still serving.
Nobody knows, but on papers he served
from 1990 till 2004.
Um
he was um their chief of
counterterrorism in Pakistan post-9/11.
Probably one of the most uh
uh important positions uh and you could
hold in CIA at that point in time
post-9/11. Um he was the one who kind of
became a whistleblower
um because he he brought to um
to the attention of the government um
the uh he spoke about uh spoke about
against waterboarding and he called it
torture. So, he was a bit of a
conscientious objector when he he he he
he he he basically called it torture and
while he himself did not do it, he he
called it out. Uh so, the government uh
obviously didn't like him for that, but
uh it gained him a lot of respect
worldwide. Um I think people listen to
John today
um for for for a guy who who who does
what is right and um um
and so so I I think his word carries a
lot of credibility.
What the Indians are going to do now and
their propaganda machine probably is is
to now wait and come out and they'll not
kind of dispute his facts. They will try
to dispute him and his credibility.
That's going to happen, but uh but
there's no going back from here. This is
too high a level and allegation. They
can't just
Right now there is dead silence. While
we are blaming Canada honestly in all
this,
imagine India has 1.5 billion people.
Its diaspora is so educated.
People getting into the CEO positions.
They know this. Now they they've seen
the evidence. They understand it.
But like there is not a single
mainstream news channel in India which
today is questioning its government
that hey, there are these people saying
this. What answer do you have? They
don't even ask a question which actually
tells you that India is not a democracy.
All this foolhardy,
you know, impressions that people carry
that India is some kind of a democracy
is is I would say like it's beyond me
because look at it like not a even a
question can be asked by their news
channels to their government. Any news
channel in India which decides to pick
this story or even ask government this
question, they won't be remain there
tomorrow. They won't see next day. It
will be off airs. And so so the Indian
regime is a very very authoritarian
regime,
uh way worse than Soviet Union. And
and the evidence is in front of you. You
will see the Indian media will keep
quiet on this.
Uh and then
uh their IT cell
and the people that they have hired in
the West, people like Terry Milewski.
Terry Milewski is actually a CBC
and
a TV anchor.
He appointed himself or and I had
announced himself as this expert on Air
India 182 bombing. But but he very
conveniently he will never pick up any
piece of information or evidence which
actually indicts the Indian government.
He very conveniently he knows that
people don't have the memory or the
patience to read these lengthy court
documents, to read these lengthy, you
know, commission reports. Who's going to
go and read all that? So, hey, I am this
TV anchor, so they'll believe what I
say. So, I'll pick up these selective
pieces of information. Look, this guy
who was charged, Talwinder Parmar, he
was the terrorist, he was the murderer.
But, he will very conveniently hide that
there are also two CSIS agents who are
claiming that hey, it was the Indian
government who was behind it.
You know, so this is called
disinformation like or misinformation I
call it because you are not kind of
technically lying, though he is lying
also in many cases and I'll point out
when he lies, but you share selective
information to build a fake narrative.
And so, he will hide all these pieces of
information he has been hiding all
through while under false belief that
nobody from the Sikh community will come
and show this evidence to the people.
You know, Sikhs, these are just, you
know, normal average blue-collared work
people who who have no idea, you know,
what's going on in the world. But, he's
mistaken, he's sadly mistaken. Uh he's
going to lose his credibility and I can
tell you today he's going to die a very
lonely man because his own kids will
know I've known that he has family. They
will know what their father did all
throughout his life, basically hide the
murderers of 329 people. So, that's why
I call like this story is as much about
these victims as much about what I call
the scum of the earth, people like Tarli
Mulaski, you know, who who kind of for
just couple of dollars will actually
betray their own country, Canada, and
then will try to hide They're They're
almost They're They're way worse, I will
tell you, than the people who actually
put the bomb on the plane, way worse.
Because these guys are smart enough to
know what's going on. And they're
deliberately doing it for their
pecuniary benefit. They're trying to
shield the Indian government. You will
see Terry Miluskey will never ever
objectively talk about all the evidence
that is out there against the Indian
government. And he's going to come out,
if he comes out now, if he dares to come
out, and he'll try to character
assassinate John Kiryakou. You just
watch it. I'm giving to you here. You
see, either he'll remain quiet on this,
or he'll come out and try to assassinate
He will never demand
that hey, Canadian government, can you
please answer
why is this high-ranking CIA official
saying this?
Never ever.
So, maybe that's what his right
punishment is.
Um that's how he he will
Sorry, I'm getting a phone call. But um
but uh yeah, I'm seeing as requested.
I'm seeing is here.
But I'm curious like um
let me um
um I'm curious I'm seeing um
how what do you how do you take when
this news came out, when you saw this
interview? What was your reaction?
Oh, I would just call call someone to
give a day.
Um yeah, I mean, I thought that it was
um
it was surprising. It kind of came out
of nowhere, didn't it? Um
though the understanding has always been
there. There are other intelligence
officials in the past from Canada and
that have, you know, made clear what
their
suspicions uh not even suspicions,
right? What their kind of conclusions
are about what has occurred, um how
India has sponsored that act of terror
that occurred. Um
I just just a couple of thoughts that I
had from listening to the entire
interview.
The first is that
he he opens the interview by discussing
the definition of terrorism, right? And
how for some reason it gets applied to
Iran, but not,
you know, any other state when
terrorism really is defined as a
political um
an act of terror or some action to
instill terror in a population
for political purposes and he he sees no
reason why you know states should not be
given the same label
and
the interviewer then asks him
Can you help us understand the context
around Iran as a state sponsor of
terror? What other examples
can you offer the audience you know to
just just have a comparison right and
um
he gives multiple of examples and then
he gets to India
and
um
and and yeah I mean you've probably
discussed a lot about what he said about
the the bombing of
Air India
but
I think it's also interesting to know
when he mentions
Israel as a sponsor of terror
and their targeted assassinations of
dissidents like the leaders of Hamas and
and you know other
um I don't know bad actors that that are
perceived by states um
and those acting against their interests
he basically says that you the reason
Israel does it is to take out
um
the leaders of of their opposition so
that those that come in place of it are
more rigid you know
and easier to assassinate politically
right and to garner support around in
attacking
and if you look at what's happened with
the the idea of um
Hardeep Singh Nijjar
you have the opposite right you have the
opposite outcome which you know I think
all six worldwide can be pretty proud
of.
Um you know, SFJ's response in carrying
on
what is in a completely non-violent
movement um that is democratic in
nature. It is not radical, right? You
don't have
replacement leadership of Hardeep Singh
Nijjar that's more rigidized, right? In
fact, they're harder to
uh critique politically and they
they um and the Sikh diaspora seems to
consolidate around those efforts. And
you see the WSO and you know, just the
general Canadian American Sikh
population
um
you know, rallying behind the cause in
in a way that is not radicalized. So
it's just really sad for India, right?
Where you know, Israel has been able to
uh
No, no, but no No, no, but but but I I
don't find a single I think honestly
like I don't find a single example where
America is blowing up its own plane and
we have so much evidence. Right. I mean,
those are false flags.
>> Okay, so No, no, but No, no, but but No,
but I I don't Yeah, assassination is
Yeah.
>> assassination
>> that's fine. I'm saying
Yeah. In uh 1975, the president signed
an executive order banning the CIA from
going around the world assassinating
people.
>> I'm I'm I am I I think I have no issue
with if India is going around and
assassinating its enemies, okay?
Every country does it.
But I will have which country Give me
one example. I don't even have North
Korea on this list.
Which is blowing up its own 329 people.
700 actually, if the other plane are
also blown up.
700 people and what is the aim?
700 of own people not technically.
Technically, they were Canadian.
But blowing them up to blame another
group of their own people.
Whom India is saying are our citizens
and they are so happy within us.
The Sikhs are if Indians, they are
really happy with us.
This kind of evil
Honestly, this is evil. It's evil beyond
you can think of.
I have not seen.
If I see an evidence, I would I would
blame that country. But I don't count
like Israel going and killing killing in
a Hamas leader is very different than
Israel coming and killing, you know,
Hardeep Singh Nijjar who is a who is a
civilian doing a referendum whom India
is saying they are part they are really
happy with us.
And or India blowing up its own plane.
Maybe Israel has blown up its own plane,
but if that evidence come, I'll believe
it. But right now we know India has
blown up its own plane.
With 260 and then and to add to this is
this irony
that
268 out of these 329 people were
technically Canadians.
And it also brought out like this
I won't call it systemic, but like there
is an element of racism.
Like you can't hide behind it. And it's
I don't blame Canada for it, but the
fact is it is there.
The Canadian Prime Minister, I am told
the Canadian Prime Minister
called up the Indian Prime Minister and
consoled him for the loss.
This aircraft took off from
Canada.
80% of the people on the board were
Canadian citizens.
Indian Prime Minister has to call up the
Canadian PM condoling him, but there's a
Canadian PM calling up the Indian PM and
it took 20 years for any Canadian Prime
Minister to even show up on the memorial
of the victims of Air India 182. 20
years.
Let's just play out a thought
experiment.
If all of these people were white,
would we have seen the same results?
Marshall can answer that. Marshall, go
ahead.
I'm sorry, I'm not getting
I'm not getting the 100%
uh
100% emoji, not getting the 100% emoji.
I don't know if I'm sure this is
working. I'm driving Kim's driving right
now, so I'm not sure if I'm coming
through or not.
No, no, we can hear you. Go ahead.
Oh,
yeah, I didn't mean to put my hand up.
But, I totally agree with that. If these
were This is a bunch of white Canadians,
this would be a done deal. People would
be in jail, right? It'd be done. It was
It's cuz they're brown. It's cuz they're
brown. So, that's another kind of
shocking thing that I've uh
only come to terms with with my country
in the last few years. I'm like, "Whoa,
racism runs deep here." And it's
systemic, right? It's It's systemic.
So, I I don't know.
Again, I don't know what to do. I don't
know what to do. I think it's
ridiculous.
Um Oh, but and I wanted to say something
to you on on Terry Milewski.
Um keep in mind, right? When when you're
when you're proposing that, you know, he
might be paid by the government of
India, it's a possibility. I totally
acknowledge that. But, keep in mind that
non-Canadians don't really understand
this.
Um how how the CBC is linked with the
federal government. It's It's kind of
this national broadcaster. It's
supported by government money.
So, they they will run interference
stories to cover up things that BS the
government. They always do that. So, you
know, so, you know, Milewski gets plenty
of compensation for doing what he does
just from his career on CBC. You know,
these are specifically chosen
individuals that get the big jobs there.
And they get access to government.
That's part of it. You know, they look
like they're But, you know, there are
very likely is
interference run in order to cover up
the government. You know, you watch CTV,
their political department is totally
different than CBC. They will ask the
right questions. They want to inform
people. CBC pretends to, but it doesn't.
So, it is very much the mouthpiece of
the
of the federal government, at least as
far as politics
and major incidents like this goes. So,
you know, that's that's important to
keep in mind with Terry. And the CBC is
also very uh
it's very underhanded about saying
exactly how much it pays its news teams.
They say one salary, but then some other
group will find out well, then there's
plus bonuses and plus this and plus
that. So, they end up being like,
you know, 10 times what they're told.
They're going to actually be 10 times in
the case of
that's how I know Mr. Dhaliwal's case.
But, there's that to keep in mind, too,
right? Is Mr. Dhaliwal probably doesn't
need any kind of carrot from the Indian
government because he gets a plenty just
from the CBC.
But, yeah, to to your point that you
were saying,
there is definitely an element of
Canada doesn't care because this
involves brown people. And I think
there's too, there's a bit of a a quid
pro quo in that.
You know, uh
Sikhs are it looks to me like Sikhs are
encouraged
to immigrate to Canada and have been for
a long time. I think maybe that's
part of it, too. There's this kind of
deal where
you know, you come over here and do what
you want, but don't expect the same kind
of justice.
Um
you know, you figure it out
while you're over here.
Kind of saying it's it's brutal just
because it doesn't involve life.
But, I I think there's a bit of that
quid pro quo going on as well.
Yeah. Yeah. Absolutely, um Marshall. And
um you know, I'm the I quite believe
with you and quite kind of honest of you
for admitting that.
Yeah, actually when I was talking about
Terry, it was in my mind and I'm glad
you brought it up that
you know in my mind that hey, he could
very well have actually been paid by CC
or the Canadian government. And he could
very well be doing all this on behalf of
the Canadian government because it's
also in their interest to to keep the
status quo.
Because if you if you look at the John
C. Major so-called
public inquiry, okay?
And which is touted by this stout
Miluski. Oh, we have this inquiry
sitting, you know, Supreme Court judge
and he's basically proven beyond doubt.
But when you read the terms of
reference,
he's forbidden from fixing the
responsibility for the bombing.
He he's forbidden from, you know,
naming or investigating into the main
conspiracy or investigating anything
into the foreign government hand.
But still, you know, John C. Major
writes up this whole thing
which makes you if you read it, there
are certain elements of it which will
make you feel as if, you know,
these Khalistani militants did it. So,
you can come away with that impression.
So, the report is also written very
very, you know, I would say shrewdly
by the Canadian establishment.
Same you can see in the court document.
So, it's like
the court document, the whole case if
you read the court's judgment, it's
available 182 pages.
Nowadays, AI is available. You can go
and read it.
There is
witness I have never
read Look, I'm not an expert, but you
read that and there's a witness saying
Ripudaman Malik came and asked me
to put this baggage with something on
the aircraft.
Then another guy comes and says he tried
the same thing with me and he offered me
money."
The girlfriend of Ripudaman Singh Malik
is saying, "He confessed to me that he's
the one who bombed the aircraft and and
then this these are the people he used.
This is how he booked tickets." So, she
laid out the whole thing.
And the judge said, "All of them are
non-credible because the girlfriend had
a tiff with the lover." And then these
two people who are saying they also had
some grudge with Ripudaman Singh Malik.
So, tell me, man, like when was the last
time you had a grudge with somebody and
you accused them of bombing an aircraft?
And and then the judge dismisses all
that in all kind of stupid logic. It's
so evident. You read it. And then he
says
very conveniently that in one line he
enters in that judgment, one line. You
have to read that judgment. In that
whole judgment, there is no talk of what
is the evidence against Talwinder Singh
Parmar because Talwinder Singh Parmar is
already dead. He lets go of all the
accused. Talwinder Singh Parmar is a
dead man. He can't be tried. Then he
says, "But we all agree that Talwinder
Parmar was the main conspirator." He
adds that one line without context,
without any discussion of evidence.
And on whose behalf was he doing it?
Like I I am amazed. Like it really puts
a question mark even on the judicial
system, the entire setup of Canada.
The judges are compromised. The the
Supreme Court, you know, judges are
compromised. Your CSIS compromised. Your
RCMP's compromised. What else?
What else these CSIS investigators has
to do? They had to come out and leak it
to Globe and Mail.
And there's also secret We didn't know.
We didn't know.
I remember like
Oh, wait. We had the the guy in charge
of the RCMP. This is last month.
The guy I'm of the RCMP is like, "Oh,
oh, we have no evidence before us that
leads us to believe that foreign
entities are interfering and foreign
governments are interfering in Canada
anymore." Flato says that in front of
everybody, right? And then everybody
loses their minds. Everybody knows
that's not true. So, you know, the RCMP
is compromised. You you know,
infiltration compromised, maybe maybe
not, but they're certainly compromised
in what they're willing to tell us and
what they're willing to admit to. So,
you know, again, this is out in the open
at this point. It's the age of the
internet. We're all seeing it in real
time. So, how much more could they have
gotten away with you know, 40 years ago
when this went all down or 20 years ago
when the trial action was? If they're
this bad now, I you know, it's like, you
know, all these people are old now,
right? They're all getting up,
you know, above 60.
So, they're they're not even with the
times. They don't even seem to realize
that what they say gets broadcast within
5 minutes to everybody who cares about
it in the whole world. So, they're still
just saying dumb stuff and then we've
got some sharp journalists finally on
the case who press them and say, "Are
you saying what I think you're saying?"
And they nail them down and they make
them say it and then, you know, a week
later, and this is the weird thing
though, right, is
CSIS comes out and says, "Well, we don't
see evidence that foreign interference
on transnational repression has stopped
and we see evidence that foreign
governments are still oppressing
Canadians." Then the guys are going,
"Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no,
all over this country. So,
you know, it's not even a might, Archi.
It is a they are. And even if the being
compromised is only, you know, they're
morally compromised and they don't tell
us the truth, they're freaking
compromised. And they're called liars
over what is happening in real time on
Canadian soil, and they're not even
trying to hide it. And when they get
outed and nailed by the press, nobody
says anything. Our Prime Minister, you
know, says things to make people proud
and forget about it. But nobody is
forgetting anything. Everybody is only
None of us are forgetting about it.
Everybody remembers it. There's just
nothing any of us can do. And it's It's
It's a nightmare.
Yeah, and and you you bring up this guy,
this I think what Marshall was talking
about. I'll just let explain that to
people
because there was a background noise
when you were speaking.
Marshall was talking about this RCMP
Commissioner
who last year did actually a press
conference
in which he basically came with another
lady officer and said, "Oh, there's so
much of crime
transnational crime going on. Indian
consulates are running these rackets
like criminal and arson that they're
involved in everything." And then just
after
11 months after that, he's coming and
saying, "Oh, we have no evidence of the
Indian state being involved."
The only thing changed between these two
cases was the government of Canada.
So, to me, now the impression is is that
the government of Canada
has so much of undue influence on RCMP
that the RCMP Commissioner can sing
whatever tone his political masters tell
him to sing.
Like, what does this say about RCMP as
an organization?
Like, what credibility does it carry?
And the same guy It's the same guy who
was sitting in this press conference
last year, okay?
Was thinking and saying today denying
all that I said, "So, we have no
evidence, okay?" And last year he was
saying, "I am sharing all this
information because I want to disrupt
it. It is so bad. I want to disrupt this
from happening. I am I I ideally should
not be talking about it. And now he's on
Canadian national TV to CBC saying, "We
just have no evidence of in any foreign
government involved in this." But
honestly, like while RCMP might be
compromised,
the fact is that these kind of things
are beyond RCMP's pay grade.
RCMP is not supposed to handle foreign
hostile actors on Canadian soil.
The job is with the Canadian security
establishment um at a national level. It
is CSIS. It is whosoever is part of the
military. Um, because what what has
happened in Kanishka was not a criminal
act. It was a hostile country doing
cross-national state terrorism on
Canadian soil.
You don't handle state terrorism through
RCMP and through court cases.
So, this whole talk in the Hardeep Singh
Nijjar case, we are going to run a case,
and then Canadian government is saying,
"Indian government should cooperate with
us." Why would Indian government
cooperate with you? Tell me.
They came and killed your citizen. What
is this like what is this talk about
that they should cooperate and then we
basically they should you know, we will
they hold them accountable. Accountable
for what?
Like they they have influence in your
country and they're exercising that
muscle. They're not going to stop.
So, the only way you can make them stop
is
make them feel the same pain that
they're making you feel.
Double the pain that they make you feel.
Which is good.
Run covert intelligence operations in
India.
Shake up the Indian government from
within.
Or if you can't do that, then you send
your army to do military coercion.
You know, you can't do neither of them
and you are basically selling this
and bull story, "We need cooperation
from India." As if India is going to
give you cooperation. And we have like
in in a newspaper, there there's a
journalist who said that Ajit Doval told
them in their face, "Even if you give us
all the evidence, we are never going to
admit it. Go.
Take a hike."
Well,
again, I feel like Cariou is also
telling us that part of the reason that
these state sponsors of terror carry out
assassinations is to radicalize those
that they are targeting, right? And
in Canada, the attempt is to paint Sikhs
as radicals, right? India's failed
pretty miserably, right? Which is why
the Canadian state has nothing to
cooperate with the Indian state over,
right? If anything, like you're saying,
they're out
It makes no sense for Canada to continue
to accommodate India within
domestically, right? When they can't
ensure that the security of those that
continue to be targeted
when
there's no reason to target completely
law-abiding,
you know, dissident citizens.
And I just wanted to concur again with
what you
had said about, you know, none of these
other state sponsors of terror have ever
carried out something of the nature that
India did. And I think that Cariou does
express that um
you know, there's other um
other things that, you know, the US,
Israel,
I think he even mentions Pakistan have
done, but nothing compares in in nature,
for sure.
Yeah, and you know, like what the what
this whatever this Canadian government
right now should be doing,
they should be actually fully backing
the separatism movement within India.
That's the way you handle India.
You don't go and do trade deals with
your enemy who's out there.
India is not in Canada. India did not
kill Hardeep Singh Nijjar.
To just come after six, India basically
showed Canada its muscle within Canada.
It is telling Canadians, we own you.
We can do this and we'll make you gulp
it.
Even if you don't want to.
Okay? That's what India is doing. It's
It's a question of Canadian sovereignty.
It is not a question of some some here
Canadian come and they've been sold this
bull. Oh, these are foreign disputes.
These are no longer foreign disputes.
Nobody's living on an island.
Okay? You can pack up every single Sikh
and send him throw him in the Atlantic
Ocean. This is not going to go away.
India will come after you and India is
not going to let you be the way you are.
So, you better pick up you better
acknowledge that India is fighting a war
with you
since 1985.
And don't be asleep on the job, Carney
or whoever that guy is. But like the
Indians openly boost boast here that
Carney is their man.
That he's financially compromised.
He has business interest.
I don't know how true that is, but
maybe that's another another topic. But
anyways, uh we have a a Simran just
dropped off. I think she was here after
quite a long period of time. I have not
listened to her. Simran, take the mic if
you can. I would love to hear from you.
>> the mic. I'm going to be stepping down.
Thank you.
Okay. Got it. Got it.
Let me invite couple of more speakers if
they they can come.
Yeah, Simran, can you hear me?
Uh so okay. Yeah, Simran, do you have
anything to add to this? Like what was
your feeling? I know you have been
tracking this Air India 182 as well and
what was What do you feel about what
John just revealed?
>> Hey, sorry. So, I could you come
I could you be for there.
Why do you give for there?
Yeah, John, that was crazy. Like you
guys are saying it's so casual. He's
very hands in the air about it. So,
I thought that was interesting and
I came mostly to listen because you have
a really coherent narrative and
everything memorized.
So, it's a good refresher.
I also wanted to say kudos to you,
Harjit. Good job for not letting this go
cuz a lot of people are not talking
about this still,
even though the narrative has evolved so
much, but people are still very afraid
to take on this discussion.
So, kudos to you and yeah, thanks for
not letting it go. Yeah, John's stuff
was excellent. Like,
I was just sitting there staring out my
window like, "How could he say that so
casually?" So, yeah, it's really great
we have like, you know, significant
speakers like Gurmeet and Alec, but
since that, there's been such a big gap
until some of your threads and videos.
So, I would hope that people just start
talking about it. And then the other
thing I wanted to mention was Did you
get the I sent you a message about that
episode 99? Like, that Brian McAndrew
after he released Soft Target, he did
media, like
video media, and it was on a TV show.
So, you don't have to do it now, but it
would be great if we could find that
recording cuz it's been pulled off air
and it's not available. And
yeah, so that's our next step is just
filling in the gaps of the timeline
knowing that all of this information was
always available and yes, there were
some failures.
Cuz you can't explain Ganeshk in just
one go. Like, even you guys are talking
about Butt Madan stuff, like he had a
video where he outwardly just denied it.
Oh, and then also I was going to say
that point about Terry Malawsky. Like,
Terry got fired from CBC, from what I
understand. So, his credibility kind of
got shot in the CBC world, too. I don't
know if they just burned him after a
while.
And so, yeah, other than that, this is
great. It's just Hello. Sat Sri Akal.
What are you guys doing?
Sat Sri Akal. Lolli party. What do you
think about
What do you think about Hello to Cohen
and everybody else and SK.
That's the guy This uh
That thing it's a bull's eye. They can
do it in like a thousand yards, right?
With 6.5 feet more, right? It's like a
That guy did a bull's eye shot at India.
And sorry you did that. Hindu saw like a
shot with it.
Right? With that like he said that that
it was done by
Huh? Daku ji, just a one sec.
I think he got all the bull's eye hit
got you.
Finish got that. He just just hit right
there.
He mentioned it twice. He made sure they
were on in the video. He mentioned like
what they did to Sikhs and stuff uh
Sikhs. I don't know what I'm saying
Sikhs cuz if there's white people
listening, but
>> Oh, yeah, but he did already. Yeah,
yeah. He dropped it twice. He made the
first seven seven comment then near the
end he did that other one, so he really
wanted to drive that point home.
And and none of the ex-cops made a video
about it. They all silent about it, you
know.
I think we're going to see a lot of
people even in our community start
having to readdress their narrative on
this or like their lack of. Like why
they haven't spoken on it. And like have
to deeply think about, you know, how to
go ahead
and start just talking about
>> I I do want to talk about that. Before I
go there, I'll take Daku cuz Daku want
to say something, but I want to put one
point to you guys and to see your
reaction. Daku ji, go ahead.
Uh Daku ji, you wanted to say something?
>> Okay, well, we wait for him to speak.
Okay, okay,
I'm I'm going to invite I see Dharma is
out there. Yeah, this is what I wanted
to really raise this point, okay,
because Dharma is here. Dharma I think
is a Malayali.
And
and I don't know whether she's
Christian. I don't know what religion
she or he formed or they kind of follow,
but Akaliji, please take the speaker. I
see quite a lot also in the listeners.
But you know, one thing that I'm really
amazed by Simran.
It's like all these evidences out there.
Now we have the CIA guy speak about it,
okay.
He's not a nobody.
But like where are all these Indians?
Like there's not a single Hindu.
Not a single Indian.
Who's talking about this and questioning
their government?
1.5 billion Hindus.
1.5 billion.
What a shame, man. What a shame.
Not a single guy.
Yeah, no one's pushed back on it yet. It
only came out what, five or six days
ago, but I still find it very strange.
>> But Simran, even before that, there was
enough evidence.
Like we had CC agents. We had Juno
Katsoulas allegations. We had
We had the sham about three four years
ago, right? I read the whole story.
All the stuff I read about it. You know,
you you
about three four years ago, right?
Yeah, but not a single
Not a single Indian. Not a single Indian
media channel.
Not a single
Like and these are like their own
people.
Like you can accuse me of being a
anti-Indian regime, but I'm not
anti-Indian people.
I feel the pain of those people who got
killed
329 innocent civilians, 329,
82 children.
You know how many elderly
killed for no reason, no reason, but
just to
frame another full entire community and
defame them and dehumanize them and
portray them as terrorist.
Whom Indian state is claiming they are
their own citizens.
Oh, they are so happy with us.
Not a single Indian has spoken up, not a
single Hindu. I can't find a single one
who has made a single post on social
media.
I am not even asking mainstream media.
Forget mainstream media.
What what about all these people like
these guys Sandeep Sita voice
They all want to claim we love India. Do
you really love India? What kind of
human beings are you?
Your brothers and sisters
children killed.
I'm going to definitely write a book on
this Simran and I made a
actually a cover for my book.
I don't know whether I already showed
that cover to you guys.
But here is the book cover, okay?
That I kind of made and I kind of made
it after a lot of thought.
Uh
Here it is.
If you if you're watching me
This is the what I what I kind of
got made was this lady. She So out of
these 329 passengers who dropped from
300 or 31,000 ft
into the cold waters of Atlantic
early morning 2:00 a.m.
Around seven or eight of them actually
when they hit the water they were alive
as per the postmortem report.
And one of the persons who were actually
alive when she hit the water and
remained alive for nine full minutes
fighting for her life
was a lady who was six and a half months
pregnant.
She and her kid, both of them survived
in that water for nine minutes.
So, this is the cover, you know, of the
book that I will make.
But imagine the people who did this.
Nobody has spoken. The only people who
came out and spoke were those two CC
agents.
Junagadh Suva wrote about his book.
But what about these Delhi Manush keys
who are actually shielding the
murderers?
All these people like Sandeep
Sita voice
and all these Indians but the sort of
world they know all these evidence. They
know their country They know their state
did it.
But they just don't have the morality
of talking the truth. Now even with John
coming out and talking about this and
telling every the whole world that this
is what has happened
like they will see they will remain
quiet.
This whole entire Indian IT cell will
come out and start basically, you know,
attacking John for speaking the truth
and telling them who was behind the
murder of their own brothers and
sisters. I don't think they consider
these these people as their brothers and
sister. I don't think they have any
feeling or pain for the victims. I think
all that these guys do this so-called
Indian nationalist is shed crocodile
tears.
Every June they will conduct a space and
do this
fake expression of oh, we are so sad for
the victims.
We are so sad they died. These
Khalistanis killed them. But in reality,
they have no feeling.
They have literally no feeling.
They're just doing it for political
purpose.
It takes about 3 minutes for the plane
to fall straight down.
When they were hit blown up,
at least took about 8 or 9 minutes
to hit the ocean, right? That's like the
most most horrific
situation you can
It's the most horrific form of death.
Yeah. That's what I'm saying. It takes
about
even if you straight dive
from 40,000 ft, it takes about 3
minutes, you know? You can imagine that
situation. That's terrible.
And you know what the postmortem tells
uh Lal Paji?
That more than half, actually 80% of the
passengers
hit the water directly.
They were not even inside the plane.
It
it damn it didn't kill the people. It
damaged the fuselage. And
and and the and the the damage happened
in a way that they actually
flew out of the aircraft. They were Even
if they were part of the aircraft, you
know, it could have still saved them
that agony of dropping by 31,000 ft.
Yeah, but that
8 Yeah, but 12 minutes of their life
last 5 minutes.
Horrific. Yeah.
Anyway, we have Dharma Dharma, how are
you? I don't know whether you heard
the interview by John, but I can play it
for you again.
And then maybe you'll hear.
Dharma, hello. Hello, Dharma.
Hey, before Dharma speaks, so sorry to
cut you off. I was wondering RG, do you
think today would be a good day to run
over your presentation or you just
wanting to focus on John?
Yeah, we can run over the presentation
as well, but I was more thinking of just
I was going to do more of these spaces
now. I think I've got rejuvenated. I
will now do it every week, okay?
But for today I was thinking talk talk
John, talk about the implications of
this.
Um yeah.
I want to say something out there, too,
today. Yeah.
Yeah, I don't know why she's not taking
the speaker, but uh maybe she's busy
somewhere.
watching this history.
Yeah. Dr. Sharma, how are you?
Hey guys. Um
Dr. Sharma, Dr. Sharma, I have
I'm just a PPL, just a private pilot.
Uh only Cessnas. I'm a commercial
Oh, yeah, I know.
Um so uh I I did uh see John Kirakous's
uh
interview.
Uh so
one thing
what you have to understand with India
uh is that and I have followed air
crashes
um aviation disasters
all over the world and
one thing that marks out India is the
sheer dishonesty.
Uh when it comes to acknowledging basic
facts.
Uh
for some reason they refuse to
acknowledge uh
basic facts which reflect badly on their
own airlines, on their own aviation
industry, etc. So,
I'm not surprised that uh
they are not even acknowledging what
John has to say.
I'm not surprised at all.
With regard to the numbers, it has to be
remembered that um
I don't know the numbers offhand I could
be wrong, but
there were 329 people
uh on Air India 182.
Only 22, the crew members, 22 were
Indian nationals.
That
290 uh 307
were foreign nationals
of which uh
295 were Indo-Canadians. That is
Canadian citizens of Indian uh
Indian uh background of Indian origin.
Uh so, majority of them, 22 Indian
nationals were on board.
The
captain and the co-pilot were both first
officer were both uh Sikh. I assume from
their names they were Sikh. Captain
Pinder is a friend and that sign is my
good friend.
The captain of the plane was my brother
we flew together, I think. Dalip, I
mean, you should you should call
Pinder's the family and ask them like
what do they think about this.
That's like a
I'm talking about when we used to fly
like uh 2001 and two.
Like uh he was in the training back in
the days.
And uh
it's been a long time since I have
talked about Pinder.
Used to be he's still my active Facebook
friend till right now.
I can ask him a couple questions if you
want me to. Sorry, go ahead. Go ahead,
Dharma, complete your thought.
Yeah, so majority of
people killed were
quote technically not Indian, right?
They had foreign passports. 307
Uh so, this became a convenient way for
India to uh shrug off
any responsibility.
Uh they could blame someone else and uh
that is why they did not target any uh
The two aircraft targeted that day, one
was AI 182 and the second one was
um I think 310 was the flight number.
No, but Dharma Dharma, I totally get the
Indian government, you know, their their
agencies, they were you know, they have
done evil acts and they were under
orders by their political establishment
to do this. But what about the Indians,
1.5 billion?
What about these people?
There's so many of them on Twitter.
Have a single
person tweeted this allegation? Single
person. Name me five out of 1.5 billion.
They reacted to the government.
Paint on walls, graffiti was more of an
issue for them than this. Yeah.
What what does this say about
What does this say about this
college educated
urban middle class coming from India?
Have they any humanity?
Or are they just
state worshipers who are now
walking zombies?
That's what I would call them, mindless
zombies. And it's it's not just AI 182,
but whatever
the incident, they will go by what the
state says. They will back the state.
That is the way
uh
they have been programmed to do. Look at
AI 171.
It is all about covering up the truth.
So,
it just happened a few months ago. And
and I will and I will use this to I know
I know Dharma, Boeing 777.
There's there's big allegations about
the state did it, right? What the hell
is that? No, but but but here is here is
one more thing.
Leave it on the ordinary people.
This is also you will see the test of
these so-called
people who
own who are basically in West.
They badmouth India all day long.
But they're doing it with a very
sinister agenda.
You see Jayant Bhandari.
Has he not seen this interview? He
knows.
But I I guarantee you today
he's not going to tweet this. He's not
going to write about this.
You know why?
Because Jayant Bhandari is the real
deal.
He is the kind of implant that Indian
state puts into West
who then basically earns the trust here
and then back stabs this whole country
and this whole, you know, system.
Jayant Bhandari,
if he's listening to me, you're not that
smart.
Okay? You He abuses Indians and India
all day. India is this, India is a
India is that. But when it
comes to the real deal,
he will never talk about it.
You will see. Talk to him about the
separatist movement in India. Say, "Hey,
okay, if India is so bad, let's just,
you know, let the people in India have
their freedom." Then he'll say, "No, no,
no, no, no, it will be even worse than
what we just today."
And then he will uh
this whole act of terrorism is blamed
against the Indian government. Jayant
Bhandari will not even tweet it once.
And you will see, I'll tag him every
single day for next 1 week and let us
see if he reacts. You will never.
He will Actually, if you go to his space
and actually pick this topic up, he will
give you 10 excuses why Khalistanis are
the problem. Okay? So So uh so this is
why, you know, you have to be very
careful. His content only matches what
white nationalists would say about other
people. So he's definitely trying to
entice people
>> So keep Keep in Keep in mind when Jayant
Bhandari is abusing Indians, he's
abusing the lower caste Indians, okay?
That's what he's doing subconsciously
while he's
So in his mind it is those, you know,
shudras and these like 85% like they are
very idiots. They are He's right. Like
he That's what he thinks about them. I
think he's misinformed. I mean, there's
so much I went through one of his spaces
uh
and he's just misinformed about
He's not misinformed about anything. He
He is misinforming you.
He is He is very much He knows exactly
what he's talking
>> about He talks about how
he completely ignores that whole the
fact that
South Indians are genetically different
from North Indians. So, it's not
something He's a He's a
He's a kind of guy who's sent here to
win the trust of the people and then
basically spread disinformation, okay?
But let let's play John's this thing
again. We also have a Kali G. I want to
play his video again.
Yeah.
I'm just going to play his a video is
already already there. I'm playing the
video as well. Um but it's on the left
hand side.
Um let me see if I've got it to the
right one. You know, the Indians support
their own Kashmiri
uh separatist groups, extremist groups.
And
and it's the Indians that blew up the
747 in Canada. It's the Indians that
carry out hits or attempted hits against
Sikh activists or or Indian leftists or
anti-Hindu nationalists in places like
Canada or the UK. There's plenty of
blame to go around. They're the second
time. He actually, you know, like it's
very interesting. And the first time he
brought it up, let me bring that up as
well.
And this was the first time he talked
about it in the interview at 7 minutes
and then he talks about it at 30 30
minute ago. But but look at others. Look
at the let's say the Greek military
junta, for example, that carried out
acts of terrorism against its own
people.
Look at Israel that has carried out
assassinations all over the world.
Or we could even point the finger at the
at the government of India for that
matter, for carrying out assassinations
and terrorist attacks in Canada, blowing
up the 747,
no less.
So, When he when he talks about like,
you know, blowing up a 747, you have to
see
um
like he the way his eyebrows go up, he
he's generally astonished that somebody
dared to do this.
blow up a 747
to just create a false flag and blame
another community for a terror attack
that they themselves have committed.
It's amazing.
It's amazing. Just imagine the whole
evil evil nature of this act.
Go ahead, Simran.
I was going to say, you know, how he
said Indian leftists? I'm curious, like
who's that group and what have what's
happened to them
and to other communities? Like we know
what's happened with the Sikhs, but John
mentions Indian leftists or
anti-nationalists.
So, is he talking about like a certain
category of people or do we have
evidence that
India has hurt them in the West, too?
Yeah, that's very interesting, actually.
I assume that he's talking about some of
the Dalit activists, like the lower
caste activists who are I know are under
threat.
Um and um yeah, it's less about them
being maybe leftists, it's more about
them being
from the lower caste and raising issues
which are of caste racism in India. Uh
with that being But that's a very good
point that Simran you bring up. But I
just want to welcome uh There are other
influences in there, right? Yeah.
I want to just welcome Akali Ji is here.
Akali Ji, Waheguru Ji Ka Khalsa,
Waheguru Ji Ki Fateh.
Uh what's your reaction on to the all
this?
Thank you. Waheguru Ji Ka Khalsa,
Waheguru Ji Ki
Fateh.
You know, I was not surprised. We've
We've been through too much.
I mean,
you know,
I think they
I mean,
my surprise is that
uh
how many countries or how many justice
systems
are left where
Sikhs can be those can help the Sikhs.
So, this is a common factor for
something.
Because the corruption is
an elite that controls the Canada and
you know
uh the influence of Israel and then the
India is really in bed with Israel and
all that.
So, where we can go? What we can do? So,
that is more of my concern rather than I
was not surprised at all.
So, maybe the US justice system is still
there that you know that can
give us an anchor that can help us.
Or maybe our own activism for our own
community to raise awareness in our own
people, you know.
And
what I feel is that this understanding
is very important in our people that
being
beside your own country, you know.
You won't get a safe haven doesn't
matter where you go.
So, we have seen that after Pilot's
death and all that.
So,
I'm kind of more
So, I have more of a kind of sad feeling
rather than
uh
and I think I would like to concentrate
on what we can do, you know, who are our
allies and
what change we can bring and do not
expect anything from Indians, I mean.
They their culture because I was born
there so I know from first hand.
Uh their culture doesn't uh
make those people, you know, in a way
that they can think beyond what they can
see.
So, any expectation from Indian doesn't
matter if he's a doctor or who but
whatever quality education he has that
is hopeless.
Uh and
the people die there every day, who
cares?
So, they're not going to care about us
or anyone else. And even mean this is a
small incident as compared to what
happened in Delhi, you know.
If that and after that the 40 years of
course and all that, so
having any expectation from them,
even a pinch of humanity, that is I
don't I think that is foolishness.
So, I'll be listening to you and I'll be
more interested in
what we can do, you know, what
physically
what we can do that can
uh bring a change and that can help us
get to our aim, you know, our own home
where we are protected and our
aspirations are
uh prosperous and we don't have to look
at Canada or any other country, you
know, without hope that they can give us
the justice. No one will give us
justice, that's for sure.
Now Nanak Ali ji, before I go to
Captain, I I tell you, I have a plan.
I know how to get get you know,
um us our homeland back.
They do see touch it all ready.
They let's get together. That's and this
is a very important message that you are
giving, okay? It's very important for
diaspora kids to realize.
The only reason Canada is not doing
anything is because these 268 people
were brown.
Just do a thought experiment. If all of
them were white,
we would not have been talking about it
like the way we are.
So, no matter how
>> I think it's in soft target. Remember
the Lloyd Axworthy.
>> Yes. Not that part, please. So, yeah, I
definitely
>> No matter like nothing against Canada,
nothing against America. We are very
grateful that we've been given refuge
and we will never forget it. We've been
given asylum.
But the fact is a fact. That's the hard
truth of life.
And it is important whether you are
first generation, second generation,
they see here, Sikh,
we have to realize we have to get our
homeland. We have to get our sovereignty
back. This should be
the only top priority of every Sikh
anywhere in the world.
Nothing else.
Else, if you are willing to live like
second-class citizens,
be my guest.
Yeah. Kaptan
>> say before Kaptan? Sorry. Go ahead.
I'm so curious now how many videos are
in the geopolitical world where this may
have been casually spoken about and we
just haven't seen it yet. So, now I feel
like watching like all these random
videos
cuz who knows? Maybe people have
discussed it and said stuff like this in
passing. But yeah, anyways, Kaptan,
Kaptan.
Yeah, no, it actually came randomly to
me. Somebody just sent it. Kaptan,
please go ahead. Thank you. All right.
Thanks, everybody. Um thanks for letting
me speak. So, a couple of points. One, I
was going to say that
um if you look at what's happening right
now, the US is using Pakistan as an
interlocutor
with
with Iran to solve the
Iran crisis.
Pakistan's role
is you really need to recognize
Pakistan's role is much greater
on the world stage now than it's been in
decades.
They've never had this kind of a role
serving as a peacemaker.
They're a key cog in
US foreign policy
as shown by these recent events.
And who does And what does Pakistan
support? Pakistan supports
the creation of Khalistan in general.
By its, you know,
um
uh
words and by its deed
in the recent in the recent past. If you
look at the creation of the Kartarpur
corridor or the um you know, sort of the
diplomatic support for Sikhs.
I I think that people who are,
you know,
sad by certain events,
I think they should just see the
desperation in the Indian
polity and the regime. The fact that
they're they're now paying
bad actors to try and take Murthys into
Gurdwaras,
right? Or to take
these,
you know,
DDT figures into Gurdwaras is how
desperate they are
to try and
bring Sikhs back into,
you know, the Hindu orbit.
That's not going to happen. And they
hate the Western
born Sikhs.
Um
people like myself and, you know, Lucy
and SK, you know,
people that talk about this stuff and
they they know that, you know, Chronos
and others like us
are pushing,
you know, this sick cause.
And, you know, we're not
we have no ties to their culture, their
Indian culture.
You know, we don't live the way that
they live, we don't think the way that
they think, and that's a threat because
they know we understand,
you know, the Western mindset because we
were born and raised in the West. You
know, we grew up in the West.
You know, we we have the Western mindset
where we're not
we're not going to be bought and paid
for,
you know, if we believe in this cause.
You know, so I think there's a few
things that have gone on. I think this
whole thing with Manipur,
when you look at what's happening over
there and the attention that's getting,
um
you know, that's and and you look at
what Indians themselves are saying that,
you know, there were some CIA
CIA operatives or other people that were
involved there. There's a level of
paranoia within these people in the
regime
that hasn't been there to date. I think
these Gujaratis are going to be exposed,
and once they lose their grip,
once they lose their grip, then you're
going to see, you know,
everybody realize that it's just a
Gujarati mafia from day one that's been
running India
according to their mentality.
And their mentality is completely
transactional. They sold their
grandmother for like, you know,
50 bucks. That's the mentality that they
have. It's all transactional. They never
People will realize that
what they've been seeing is from day one
with all these Nehrus and
Mahatma
Gandhi, they're all these Gujarati
people
that have run this run that country from
day one and have destroyed it and have
lied
about the poverty rates. They They have
lowered the level that it takes to
qualify as, you know, being poor just so
that they can meet some metrics. They've
stopped entering any um
you know, international competitions
that involve, you know, uh education and
things like this.
They They don't want to
be exposed, but they're being exposed
daily. And you see online in the X
spaces.
There's so many people that
you know, basically have a
expressed a common cause with Sikhs. And
I posted something the other day just
like, look at these people dumping milk
into lakes and rivers and everything
else. And at the same time they're
drinking cow urine.
You know, and you know, do you want to
believe what those people say about
Khalistan, about Sikhs, about anybody
that wants to break up India? Or do you
want to
Or do you want to listen to the people
that say that that is satanic or demonic
or
just on its face it's absurd.
Who dumps milk into a lake or a river, a
culture?
And they support it. Bar none. You know,
this concept. You see it all the time
with all the that they're throwing
in all the lakes and the rivers,
destroying the environment. Are you
going to believe those people?
You know, that Sikhs are so such
extremists. We just don't want to be
around them and their culture. Captain,
I have a question I have a question for
you. Sorry to interrupt your thought,
but like
>> ahead. Do you Do you think like John's
um
uh the statement um Do you think it is
premeditated or do you think it just
came off the cuff? No, no, that's 100%
premeditated. He had to have had some um
clearance. Like once you're in the from,
you know, everything that I've have I'm
not a part of the CIA, so I don't know.
Maybe it's different, but once you're
part of some kind of intelligence
network agency like that, you don't just
go off the cuff. You can't go rogue like
that.
You know, and say things that
you know, you don't have that knowledge.
They could sue him.
You know?
Why aren't they suing the guy for
basically implicating them in the Air
India bombing? Saying that they Why
isn't the Indian government suing him?
If if this was so, you know, egregious
or he was so defamatory or if he was
wrong, he's lying, he's being
>> They They They They never sued the Globe
and Mail as well.
For even Tarik Kashmiri for alleging If
you If you take it to a court of law,
Yeah. there's something called
discovery. Correct.
>> They'd have to They'd have to answer
questions under oath and provide
evidence. Correct.
And the other side has evidence. They
have proof. Now, I've done a lot of a
lot of thought exercise with it.
Um, Grok, asking it about these kinds of
things, and Grok always gives these
milktoast kind of Indian regime's
friendly answers until you start really
probing Grok and telling it, "Answer me
about David Kilgour. Yeah.
>> Tell me why wasn't he allowed to
testify? Yeah. Tell me why the major
inquiry
had limited terms of reference. Tell me
about the pattern of behavior with
respect to um, you know, the detention
of Sikhs. Why don't you uh, you know,
and I I basically try and get Grok to
finally admit that yeah, you know,
there's a pattern of behavior and and
eventually Grok always And I tell Grok,
"Tell the truth.
If you're a truth-seeking engine, which
you say you are,
then come across with, you know, what a
rationalization that explains all of
these things." And then it it it
invariably,
so far in my experience, when
questioning Grok on these points and why
it's answering in a certain way.
Eventually, it always comes around and
says, "Yeah, you know, um
I will start to incorporate PNR into
this conversation. I will start talking
about, you know, um
patterns of behavior."
>> so Captain, to that earlier question,
like if it was premeditated, uh so
you're you're you kind of believe that
it's kind of almost at a systemic level,
basically. He was not even acting in at
as an individual. He This was somebody
gave him a signal to to do this. Yeah, I
think President Trump has basically
signaled to all of us,
you know, all of the things that he said
from that first We had that space after
Modi came begging with a bowl in hand
after Jay Shankar sat all tight
Mar-a-Lago trying to get a meeting.
You know, he came to the and he they
were embarrassed, you know, um
on so many levels in that meeting where
they they asked this idiotic question
and then they then the the the the notes
that were put out afterwards and they
talked about, you know,
um
terrorism and criminal behavior and all
this kind of stuff. I remember we did
the space. I I wish we'd record these
spaces, but that one wasn't recorded,
I'm pretty sure. Regardless, I think
it's from pattern of behavior and then
you saw this the conflict with Pakistan
and and India. Got it. Got it.
>> we're we're going from six planes to
seven planes to 10 to 11 planes. Yeah.
Got it. I'm going to
I have a lot of questions. Captain, I
have a lot of questions. But one one
thing. President Trump has not spared
any opportunity to embarrass these
people and he does it by saying Modi's
his friend. So what's what's Modi going
to say that Trump's, you know, um hates
Modi? No, he says, "Modi's my friend."
all the time, but yet he embarrasses
India on every at every turn, you know,
and and including saying that we'll
allow India to buy oil from Russia for a
month or two months. And Indians are
losing their minds. These Indo-phobes
people are losing their minds and
Captain, we'll Yeah, we'll bring the
geopolitics into it, but I want to make
sure that people are and I'll come back
to you. I have some other questions on
this, but Dharma you had your hand
raised and I want to kind of keep make
keep sure that people who are joining
late that just to refresh everybody's
memory why we are talking today is that
we have CIA high-ranking official John
Kiriakou actually come on live TV
and in the past we've had
Canadian intelligence investigators
alleged to grow and mail but they never
showed us their faces. Uh we've had
Junuk Atrua write it in his book, but he
kind of leave it hanging there, but now
we have a CIA official
come publicly official like we can see
him in flesh and blood alleging what is
now common knowledge in the intelligence
circles which is that India was behind
the Air India 182 bombing.
So we are discussing that and and
discussing the implications of that.
Dharma, please go ahead. You had your
hand raised here.
Yeah, thanks
so two points I wanted to make.
One is that yes, John is certainly
uh his statements right now are
certainly part of a larger plan. I
believe that. Um
uh I'll come back to this later, but
before I forget last time on the last
place I was going to mention this
but there was a book written by a former
intelligence
official called
uh Maloy Dhar. I read it in 2006 or
something like that. Open secret. Open
secrets, yeah. Yes, Maloy Dhar. He was
not RAW,
but IB IB Uh he was IB, right? So India
has two intelligence agencies IB and
RAW. So he was part of RAW and these two
agencies are
it's the worst kept secret in India that
these two are
almost openly at conflict with each
other.
Uh so
his comments at the time many were
dismissing it as rivalry with other
intelligence agencies operating in
India.
But very important points he made which
aviation observers like myself and even
law and others would understand.
If you look at these hijackings that
Maloy Dhar says were false flags.
There were four or five hijackings of
Indian Airlines flights.
In the 1980s.
Even before 1984.
There were three or four.
I'm sorry I don't remember the numbers
but Maloy Dhar has gone into great
details on that on how these were false
flag operations.
One of them even had a former NSA
Subramaniam.
I think the Airbus 300 which was
hijacked to Dubai.
Via Lahore.
I see 421 I think.
That even had Subramaniam who later
became the NSA.
On board as one of the quote unquote
passengers.
Which he goes into great details about
how these were false flags supposedly
done by Babbar Khalsa and.
I don't remember the name of the other
federation but which was claimed to be
Khalistani separatists.
And he goes into great details about how
these were false flag operations. Which
makes it pretty interesting reading
especially when as an observer of
aviation who has observed hijackings and
other such things from reports from very
closely who has read these reports. I
find these three or four hijackings very
suspicious. Yeah no but Dharma
I'll I'll kind of intervene. I have read
that book. I think it's an excellent
point you bring in.
Everybody should buy this book. It's
called
Open Secrets and the writer is M.K.
Dhar, Maloy Krishna Dhar. He was uh the
Deputy Director of Intelligence Bureau,
the actually the most powerful
intelligence organization India has. RAW
is not as powerful as IB. IB is the
domestic intelligence, but it also does
uh external intelligence. And um so uh
he was high as you can get. And he wrote
this book and this book was published
just 5 months before his death. And in
this book is actually banned in India.
Imagine. And uh his son uh who is no
longer a you Indian citizen, um his son
is actually I think a UK citizen.
He then worked very hard to get it
published and uh if you can get a hand
on that book uh highly highly
recommended because the the main crux of
that book is not the revelations he's
making. He made a lot of revelations,
but the main crux of that book is that
he's making a plea to the international
audience that they have to intervene in
India. He basically makes a case that
the Indian agencies are rogue to a level
that CIA and even KGB cannot be.
And his main argument is this
that the Indian agencies are totally
unaccountable, totally unaccountable
because uh CIA and SIS and even MI6, all
these agencies are formed by an act of a
parliament and they are at the end of
the day, yes, people can argue like
there are like question marks that they
have a lot of discretion that they
misuse, but they can be called up by the
Senate anytime. And in America you see
like the CIA chief being called by the
senators like every third day. And kind
of you know, he has a budget.
Uh there is they talk about slush budget
and all, but you know, that slush budget
is slush budget. It it's not a slush
budget from the government. The he has a
budget he has to kind of adhere to. He
has to and he can be held accountable.
But M.K. Dhar makes a argument that the
Indian intelligence is totally
different. It has no budget. It has a no
boss. It only reports to the Prime
Minister who changes every 5 years and
it had it is not bound by any act of the
Parliament.
It is basically a mafia and it's a mafia
like no other and he makes a comparison
with CIA and MI6 and he basically says
that the if left unchecked these two
agencies RAW and IB will cause havoc in
the world that the world does not know
what it is doing.
And and I agree with him and I think
that the whole world has to intervene
like this this is a prime example. I
think when John John Kiriakou in this
interview talks about blowing up the
747, you have to see his eyes.
He is actually astonished that somebody
did this like for their own people.
To blame their other group of own
people.
Unheard of. I have not heard North Korea
do this act with their own people. If
they have, please provide me evidence.
Okay? But India is one such country and
and people call it the most democracy. I
don't know. I don't know with what face
they call it a democracy but but anyways
SK had the hand raised and then we'll go
to Akali. SK go ahead.
Good. Yeah, Dharma complete your
thought. Dharma complete your thought.
Yeah, that's fine.
It's about AI 182 and there were
actually a plan to blow up two planes
that day, AI 182 and AI 310.
310 could not be blown up because the
bomb blew up on the ground itself.
Both these it was a coincidence that
baggage
x-ray baggage at Vancouver and
at Montreal Air India's
x-ray baggage facilities
at
all three points, Vancouver, Tokyo,
Montreal
all failed
on that particular day.
And there was specific uh
specific
uh
intelligence about uh some something
like this happening.
The baggage failed and yet the flight
was allowed to proceed.
And the baggage was checked through when
there are specific instructions given by
Air India security that
uh in case the X-ray baggage doesn't
work, the baggage will be left behind.
In spite of that, this one baggage was
checked through when 29 other baggages
were not checked through because of the
rules in place when the X-ray baggage is
not uh
uh working.
I mean, there are so many questions that
when you read the Air India 182 report
and the 310 Air India 310 report in
detail,
these red flags pop up.
The question is, why aren't these red
flags being talked about? I think I
should write a detailed post on it uh
soon, blog on this very soon.
Yeah, and I can give you uh
Dharma, I have created an AI space
database and I have uploaded all the
court documents, all the inquiries, all
the evidence, soft book PDF, everything.
You It had 82 sources.
And uh and you can ask it any question
and do any analysis on top of it. Uh but
uh yeah, I have actually a 3-hour 2-hour
live stream I did talk where I talk
about only the misses at the airport,
okay?
If you forget everything else, the money
paid to Ripudaman Malik by the Indian
government. If you even ignore the
allegations by CC investigators, you
ignore
um the the sham uh public inquiry
commission, you ignore the the whole
court case with all the evidence till
the accused were
made to walk free. You ignore even John
John's allegations here. Just look at
what happened at the airport. That
itself will tell you, "Hey, this is an
intelligence operation going on."
Probably with the full connivance of
even Canadians.
And um it's mind-boggling how these
bombs got on the the bag got on to not
one aircraft, it got on to an aircraft
in Vancouver, traveled without passenger
from Vancouver to to Toronto, and then
Toronto it got on to another aircraft
without a passenger. And from there the
aircraft went through another airport.
And it got delayed by 3 and 1/2 hours.
The X-ray machine gets it doesn't get
X-rayed because X-ray machines
mysteriously stop working 15 minutes
before this bag is to be scanned.
The uh once this bag goes through
without X-ray scanning, the X-ray
machine comes back live again, and the
X-ray technician who came to check the
machine he could never find any fault.
He could say, "Hey, I don't know how it
went off and how it came back on." The
dog squads all the dog squads of Toronto
are on training going to Vancouver on
that particular day. The security
officer of Air India is not available
only for that day. A temporary security
officer from New York has come in. And
that temporary security officer gives a
fake demo to the security staff which
allows them to actually not even use the
sniffers properly. And they allow this
bag to go through even after the sniffer
is beeping primarily because of the demo
given by that security officer. And that
security officer refuses to call the
backup dog squad. Toronto airline calls
the
sorry, Canada airline calls the backup
air squad. The security officer, the
Indian airline security officer refuses
to wait for 15 more minutes to have the
backup dog squad arrive and orders the
plane to take off after fighting with
the airport authorities. This is how
this aircraft got into the air with the
bomb.
And it's just amazing. There were bags
offloaded. There were bags that because
of the X-ray machine failure
uh
the bags some were bags could not be
loaded on because there's a specific
rule that says that if it is could not
be X-rayed, it will it will be sent by
the next flight.
And so there were around 29 bags that
were not sent on the flight, but this M
Singh, uh, this one bag which had been
Without the passenger?
Without the passenger on a Canadian
Pacific flight, it arrived from
Vancouver, and it was checked through
even without, uh,
being checked again because of the x-ray
machine failure. Other 29 bags get
pulled out, but this bag gets on board.
Okay. No, no, and no, no, but but this
bag was actually caught by the baggage
checking guy. His statement is on
record. Canadian Pacific guy. Yeah, no,
no, not Canadian Pacific, the secure the
security guy, the who actually was
scanning, then they use handheld
scanners, okay?
And he said that when my handheld
scanner was on this bag, I heard the
beep, but this Indian Airlines security
officer grabbed the scanner from his
hand
and said, "You are doing it wrong."
He lit a matchstick, took the matchstick
right next to the scanner, and the
scanner started giving a whistling
noise.
Okay? Because the fumes were too close,
and he told this guy that, "Hey, you
will actually get a full whistling
noise, not a beep."
Okay? And because he gave that demo, he
said, "I was so afraid when this bag
beeped, this guy has just given me a
thrashing that it has to be a whistling
noise, I did not have the courage to
take the bag out. If he had not given me
the demo, I would have immediately taken
this bag out."
Okay? So, there's a lot that happened on
that airport. We will do a full, like, a
episode on that, and uh, but leave that,
like, for just focus on if the CIA
official gone mad?
Like, okay, the CIA John Kiriakou might
have gone bonkers. Let's assume that.
Do two CIA agents, investigators who
actually investigated, who actually went
to Global and Mail and gave the whole
story out of like how money was paid to
Ripudaman Malik, how Ripudaman Malik
basically hired foot soldiers to get the
bags onto the plane. Was all that also
those two CSIS agents also gone mad?
Okay, fine. We assume those also gone
mad. What about Juno Katsuya? He writes
in his book that Indian government did
it. Has he gone rogue? Okay, let's
assume he's gone rogue. What about the
judge who heard all this evidence in the
Supreme Court against Ripudaman Malik,
against Bagri, against Reyat, and he
still lets go all these accused walk
free?
Like just read the court case for hell's
sake. Go and read the amount of
evidence. It's all out there.
Ripudaman Malik
girlfriend tells you this is what how he
said he he got he arranged the people.
This is how much money he paid. This is
how he booked the tickets. This is how
they got the bags on the aircraft. This
is the person's car they used. All
thrown out of the window
because you Indian agents couldn't be
put to jail because then you know the
India's name will come out.
So so like come on like who are there's
too much things too much stuff out there
right now for the Canadian government to
act innocent, ignorant, or to use
propaganda,
you know, propaganda. I don't know what
you call pimps like Terry Miluskey to
muddy the waters, to mislead and
disinform the people. The cat is out of
the bag.
Cat is out of the bag. Whosoever is
there in Canada, okay? It's out of the
bag. It's not going back in the bag.
It's there.
You you will need a new world order to
put it back in the in the in the in the
bag. So so you better like and and first
of all hats off, okay? I just want to
take
I I do want to kind of acknowledge the
courage of people, man. Courage of
people like people like those two CSIS
investigators who went and shared all
the information with
Zuhair Kashmiri Globe and Mail, okay?
And people like Terry Gluskin, they come
up and they basically try to
discredit them saying, "Oh, these are
anonymous sources who came to Globe and
Mail." No, they are not anonymous. This
is where he's a liar. Terry Gluskin,
he's lying through his teeth. He knows
very well these are not anonymous
sources. These are called in journalist
world, they are called confidential
sources.
People who come McAndrew and Kashmiri,
right?
>> Yes. No, no, not McAndrew and Kashmiri.
The two
CSIS agents who The reporters were
McAndrew and Kashmiri. Yeah, the
reporters were McAndrew and Kashmiri.
But but they were not just kept They
were not just McAndrew and Kashmiri.
They were They when they were writing,
they were fully employed by Globe and
Mail and Toronto Star.
So So basically
they the two top journalists from the
two highest selling dailies in Canada.
Okay. Doctor, can you just mute your
mic?
Yeah.
So
So the CSIS agents came to them and gave
them this whole story of how this was
done.
And people like Terry Gluskin
these scum of the world, they claim that
oh, they try to discredit by these fake
lame excuses. Oh, these were anonymous
sources. No, the Soft Target book
does not quote anonymous sources.
The people
it's confidential sources. And anybody
who has
anything to do with journalism or media,
they know when journalists of Globe and
Mail write something in their name
with the name of Globe and Mail behind
them
they're the full legal department which
will check whether these people who are
claiming they're CSIS agents, whether
they are correct or not. Otherwise, they
will not let them publish that book. The
publisher will check. Otherwise, they'll
get sued for millions of dollars for
defamation
for spreading false information. They
can't They won't be able to write again.
But the Indian government was never able
to sue Zuhair Kashmiri. Why? Because
they know if they sued
Globe and Mail or Zuhair Kashmiri or the
publisher of that book then they would
have to show who their confidential
sources were.
And that is the reason why John C. Major
when WCSO
made a representation to the John C.
Major commission that we should call
Zuhair Kashmiri, we should call Brand
McAndrew to the public inquiry
commission, make force them to reveal
their sources. The John C. Major flatly
refused. He said, "It's not my mandate
to fix responsibility for the bombing.
It's out of my mandate."
What a farcical inquiry so-called.
And these idiots like Terry Miluski have
the gumption. They think the whole world
is so fooled that they can come and tell
the whole world this lie that this
inquiry fixed everything and they have
fixed the responsibility for the
bombing. Whom are they fooling?
People can go and read that John C.
Major inquiry report. See where John C.
Major himself has written, "I cannot
call these witnesses. I am not allowed
to fix the responsibility for the
bombing."
Okay, but I I know they had a
but I want to acknowledge the bravery of
these CSIS agents who went to Globe and
Mail.
Sardar Tara Singh Hayer, he was murdered
because he would have been the most
credible witness against Ripudaman
Malik. Um the the
quote unquote platonic lover of
Ripudaman Malik she went and
risked her entire life. Nobody today
knows where she is.
She's probably under some witness
protection. Maybe she even killed by
now.
And she risked everything to come and
spill the beans on Ripudaman Malik. Mr.
A and Mr. B whose identity we don't know
who spilled beans on Ripudaman Malik and
how he was he was out there trying to
arrange people to put bombs baggage on
the on the aircraft.
There's also Mr. Narendra Gill who gave
who didn't care that his name was being
openly shown on the on the court case.
He gave testimony against Ripudaman
Malik.
We we have to acknowledge the courage of
John
John Kiriakou Kiriakou.
And you know and and I'm sure many
others.
Uh just one sec. Just one sec.
The point he made about mainstream media
is good though. Absolutely did. will not
publish a story unless they have a
second source even a third. So even if
they know that their information is good
they still need a second source to
validate and then they can go with a
story.
It's a pretty great point.
Yeah, there's another El Capitan who has
come I'm pretty sure he's a
he's an Indian. Captain I think he's he
got muted and he made a second one.
Okay. Okay, got it. I don't know why
that happened but I can
I can add him.
Uh but hey Coin is here finally. Coin
I've been missing you. I have not seen
you for so long. I hope everything is
okay. Chardi Kala.
Yeah good good thanks. Um Waheguru Ka
Khalsa Waheguru Ki Fateh. Waheguru Ki
Fateh. that John Kiriakou finding that
you found Harjit Singh is just I think
you know there's
divine timing sometimes. Um
that was I think really fortunate
because John's also getting
a lot of kudos just generally at the
moment. His podcasts
are huge.
He gets interviewed by some of the
I'd say really prominent truth tellers
on social media in general. So what he
says is is taken
um you know, I think quite seriously.
So, having someone like that make this
statement is and not once, twice, and
quite convincingly, you know, um I think
it it does bode well for us. And I think
what we also now need to be doing, you
know, and I think you're doing you do it
quite well, is to actually put this
information out more, I think,
systematically because
there's
it's a great opportunity to do that
because like you said, you we've had
previously people who have and and
they've been quite fortunate who've
written books because
why the Canadian government
and what what actions and their
non-actions of what is state terrorism,
why it wasn't and hasn't been taken
seriously.
And you know, that's a discussion we we
can have, but you know, we also can't
forget that there was, you know, the
actions of the Indian government wasn't
just um obviously
the the Canadian bombing of the 747.
There was other planned
um
uh bombings as well.
And that was highlighted really
carefully and clearly
in um
in the book by the Canadian MP.
Um sorry, I just had it up before. I'll
bring it up. Yeah, David Kilgour, yeah.
Yeah, that's right. So, David Kilgour's
book is really important, I think,
because what it does
highlight that, you know, within this
special meeting that took place um and
that was referred to as an international
corporation benefiting respective
governments. And if you look at the
individuals that were part of that
um conspiracy to basically create
another bombing in Europe of an Air
India plane
to blame the Sikhs.
Now
that is quite serious because you had
that incident and then you had another
false flag that was being attempted or
blame being attributed to is in the
killer case. So you've got you got three
cases there.
Three opportunities to to to push
forward this narrative that the Sikhs
are extremists and terrorists at a time
when the Indian government was
committing
genocide
um horrific genocide the Sikhs in
Punjab.
So and that's a pattern that
authoritarian regimes do because how do
you deflect from their crimes against
humanity? They go after
authorities that are, you know, outside
who are raising awareness and that was
really really serious and I think
Kilgour's book in particular um
does raise something that even um you
know, John Kirakou raised about using
cutouts.
Um these are these sort of actors state
actors because those people weren't
state actors. I think they were just a
criminal syndicate because of you know,
there was a neo-Nazi person who um for
example used to take money to create
terrorism crimes.
There was two Sikh gentlemen that were
there. There's someone else who was
identified as an Italian and and the
whistleblower who was a a Russian
defector who was working
um
you know, with CSIS at the time and
maybe it'd be interesting
why he was sent. Was he just sent cuz he
did actually
um
he did report it to the police the very
next day and that's how that plan
fizzled. But it was quite a serious plan
of bombing another airline to blame the
Sikhs.
And that's
>> it's it's really Yeah, I'll give I'll
give It was really serious, right?
>> Yeah, going to I'll give people a quick
rundown because I totally remember that
plot. So the plot was like this. The
Canadian intelligence
has this spy on their whatever roles and
they tell him we have a job for you.
And as per him he's sent to Germany, I
think.
And then uh they they are Indian friends
are asking for some help. You have to
help this guy bomb an aircraft or help
him do some act. Then he goes there and
then I don't think he was told initially
that bombing an aircraft and then he
said I reached there. I get into this
big apartment complex and I get into
this room and I see these Sikhs. I will
not name the person he saw. People can
read his book.
Uh who are totally dressed up and then
we have these German intelligence
officer and they're planning to bomb an
aircraft. And he said when I heard their
plan, this is what I have to supposed to
help them.
He said I developed cold feet because
what hap what happens to me now?
And uh if these guys will end up bombing
the aircraft like um you know and he
didn't trust CCs completely. So he
wanted to get out of that quagmire. So
what he did was
he traveled to another country close by
in Europe where he was wanted for a
crime. And he said I can then go there
and have myself arrested. That way I can
give an excuse to CCs I can't help these
guys because I got arrested. Okay? So so
he travels to this other country and
just kind of shows himself up and lo
behold the police there arrest him and
he's put behind the bars where he was
wanted for a couple of years and he
remains there in bar. And um and then
the CCs basically complain that we know
that you deliberately got yourself
arrested. So, so that's the whole story
in that book. But, uh, it kind of, um,
corroborates Just to clarify, I don't
think it's it's hard to know if there
was other intelligence or whether there
were some people who were observing
because there was a German man who
chaired it. There was an Italian
identified as Dr. De Marco. There were
two Sikhs. There was Prasada himself who
was called his alias was Robert Fisher.
And he was sent at that time by CSIS.
Um, whether it was just to sort of, you
know, they've heard of another plot
happening to try to understand it. We
don't know. Like, we don't really shoot,
you know, that's just sort of, um,
talking.
But, I think, you know, he described the
plot as being macabre even for someone
in his line of work. And he went back to
the hotel and he would have informed,
um, you know, CSIS. And I think he was
advised to his own volition, he,
you know, he informed the Italian
police. And they came and sort of
disrupted that. Now, what I think what's
what's sort of important is that during
the during that meeting, what they were
talking about was that, um, it would
they were trying to push forward this
this agenda that it was international
cooperation. But, it wasn't. And I
think, you know, in line with what
Harcharan Singh Brar, Brian McAndrew,
um, you know, the fact that you have an
ex or a former Canadian MP, David
Kilgour, like, they've all come on board
and said saying that India India's role
orchestrated the 1985 bombing of Air
India Flight 182 182. Now, that's not
These aren't small names or small, you
know, people. Like, and I think, you
know, when you've got even the FBI and
now you've got CIA agents coming out and
saying that like it's a pattern of
information.
Particularly now with I think India's
transnational repression and terrorism
um history
which is only getting
Did she cut out?
Yeah, we just lost her. She dropped the
mic.
She was a listener and then I hope
there's not her battery. We still have a
second and then Yeah, and then we can go
to Captain. Yeah, go ahead Simran. Okay,
sounds good. So the only the other point
that I forgot to make was I think Acar
said this before and I think all of you
have said this in a way in some way.
So like they've already spoken about so
much, so why didn't they take any credit
for this when that is the culture like
when you do so that
that they're open about it.
And I kind of butchered the way I said
that.
>> Yeah. Yeah, and then yeah, and I'll just
plug in couple of books for people to
read.
Um so
people who can watch me on my live
stream.
Okay, for some reason I can't show it.
Let me see if I can get a shirt. Yeah.
So okay. Yeah, this is the book. There
are two books in my hand. You can see.
The first one is a soft target which was
published in 1988.
Then a revised version was published I
think in 2005
immediately after the criminal trial for
the case was over. It's identical books.
There not a single word was changed.
Only thing is they added a preface.
And the preface basically told says,
"Didn't we tell you so in 1988 that
nobody would be punished?" Because the
Canadian government has already decided
to curry favor in hand. Nobody can be
punished for this.
And the preface basically then
kind of tells you what happened in the
court case and why they didn't punish
anyone and any new information that came
out in the court case. But basically the
whole court case was trying the same
people that the book had published. This
is the book I I recommend people should
buy it. Soft Target.
The India It says Soft Target, India's
intelligence service and its role in the
Air India disaster.
And this is a revised version that got
published. And the initial one that was
published in '88 was how the Indian
intelligence service penetrated Canada,
Soft Target. So uh people should buy
this book. There's
And then another thing uh
similar to your point, I was recently
reading a book
by the DGP of Punjab. He was one of the
DGPs, the top cop in Punjab in India,
where the persecution of Sikhs was done
by the Indian state. And he wasn't a
state employee.
His book is called Identity and
Survival.
And you know, in in that book he details
that every single incident of terrorism
in Punjab
which involved killing of the Hindus was
done by the Indian state.
A DGP is elected
>> called? The book is called Identity and
Survival, from the murder of A.S. Atwal
to the Talwandi bus killing to the
murder of three Hindus that were taken
out of the bus and killed again, to the
murder of Longowal. He basically lists
out all these actions saying these were
all the acts of the Indian state. And he
interestingly also talks about third
agency.
Okay? And that's another book to read,
Identity and Survival by Kirpal Dhillon,
DGP, okay? No less. Then there's another
book
by A.R. Darshi, Ajit Ram Darshi.
He was joint secretary of Punjab
government.
He in his book, his book is called The
Gallant Defender.
He was a joint secretary. He was in the
thick of things happening in Punjab in
the '80s, okay?
He in his book
did not even lay out that okay, all
these killings in Punjab were being done
by the Indian state. He actually named
the officers
that okay, so and so killing of Hindus
so and so RAW officer V.I. Vasudeva here
so and so RAW and IB officers so he's
written it down, documented it in the
book.
And
so those are the two books worth
reading. I'm actually just got hold of
those books so I'll be sharing a lot of
that information. So agency is that
referencing some type of Indian Yeah.
>> third party or like a different
>> Yeah, so so basically what the Indian
state did was to the the the whole this
all of this persecution of Sikhs
Kanishka bombing
Blue Star, all the planning of this had
started in '79.
And to keep it utmost secret and it they
created a separate agency called third
agency. It was not IB, not RAW.
Intelligence officers from IB and RAW
were taken and a third agency was
created. It was a law onto itself.
It was being directed directly by Prime
Minister Indira Gandhi and her four main
confidants, Sanjay Gandhi, Fotedar, uh
Arun Nehru and one more guy.
And these guys were directing this third
agency and they were above the law. The
Chief Minister of Punjab didn't know
what was happening. Even the Home
Minister was not told. Everything was
controlled by them through the third
agency. So interesting, you read that
book and you'll come to know how they
did all these acts of terrorism, state
terrorism.
>> the third agency and Ajmer Singh
Randhawa, you know there is a pamphlet
called Preetama. Yeah.
>> Uh Ajmer here, he wrote about it too. I
put it in the book. Got it. Got it.
Okay, let's go to we have a Falcon in
the I know we had
I think Captain you had your hand raised
before I go further.
Yeah, you can let Falcon go first. He's
I think he's a new speaker. Okay, Falcon
go ahead.
Uh good morning, guys. It's morning time
here in Europe, so I hope everyone is
doing good. Yeah, good good good.
Yeah, so I have only few things to
raise.
We all knew that there was Indian
involvement in the killing of these
people in the air.
The bombing of this Air India.
So, if you guys know like I think it was
1 year ago or around when the CT of
nature and after that so Australian
government
I think deported three to four people
who were like doing a wrecky of
airports.
They were keeping an eye on the ground
staff. So,
they were planning to do something
similar like
Air India bombing from like which had
gone from Canada to was going to from
Canada to London.
So, I mean on that time the hype was
very up. I mean the by nature killing
and uh Assin Kandh and all all these
things were very new. So, they wanted to
do the same thing like they did in the
back. So, they wanted to put everything
back in the ground. They wanted to cover
everything up with the dirt.
So,
I know many things people are here from
Canada.
But, I will expect anything from the
home country
because UK till now
by the Assin Kandh died
they did not have any like official
inquiry.
People knew that is assassination.
So,
I don't know. I I don't know what to
expect from the Commonwealth countries.
And second of all,
Uh excuse me?
Yeah, that what I can tell you what to
expect.
I can I I can tell you what to expect.
Expect them to be turned into third
world holes by India in next 15
years.
That's what to expect. And that's what
their future is. That's where they're
headed. Um because they can't stand up
for their own sovereignty. And they want
to kind of, you know, um
um be friendly buddy-buddy with the mass
murderers. So be it, you know, um
they'll they'll be for it. And um
And I can I can tell you like right now
like like you you bring up a right point
on aviation terrorism. Like I think
Lucy's there down there.
I think it was she or somebody going
from your group of girls who who made a
very good point that when it comes to
aviation terrorism, there's no match of
the Indian state and agencies.
And they have been involved in all these
kind of acts like these hijacks.
Yeah.
We we we don't have evidence of Israel
like but with India we have enough
evidence.
And um
And then, you know, like um
uh there was a like a there were all
these hijacks plus you talk about
Australia. I think there was one more
incident which um if I'm not wrong um
yeah, it's not it's cannot hitting my
memory yet but it'll come back. Yeah, uh
um The 1983
bombing in in India which had very early
similar baggage handling um I'll say
strategy. Yeah.
>> And that was blamed on the Elam Tamils
or who claimed responsibility.
>> that is correct. Yeah, same. That was a
weak case because that that group which
claimed responsibility had just formed
and then immediately disbanded after
that bombing and they were all
discharged. And one key conspirator
only went to prison for less than 2
years. So, that was a really strange
case. Um actually actually
Um as cases are really interesting, I
was just looking at the links between
Israel Mossad and India. And um in 19 uh
when
RAW was created, um Indira Gandhi
actually explicitly advised um uh uh uh
uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh
uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh
During the 1971
Indo-Pakistani War, Israel supplied
India and the Mukti Bahini with mortars,
ammunition, military instru-
instructors.
Um Israeli arms manufacturer
played a key role. And this was actually
kept secret due to India's public
stance. In the late '70s, covert
contacts continued under
Prime Minister Desai. In '79, he
secretly invited Israeli Defense
Minister Moshe Dayan to India,
where he traveled discreetly to avoid
public notice. These were low-profile uh
uh uh uh uh uh uh um
uh
uh links. And um and in the '80s, there
was deeper training, security
cooperation, and operational ties.
So, and that expanded under Indira
Gandhi, who returned Prime Minister in
1980. Um so, that included aid three
counterterrorism training. So, there's
about 20 Indian special group. So, I
don't know if they were part of that
third agency. Um so, they were
commanders from the 56 Commando Company.
Um they received 3 weeks of intensive
training at Israel's secret Sayeret
Matkal
um base
with Mossad commandos and they led the
famous 1977 Entebbe hostage rescue.
So, they coordinated the program um
despite lack of diplomatic ties. These
commanders later took part in Operation
Blue Star
in the '84 raid and uh
of of Golden Temple and the
and and around um obviously Punjab.
Post assassination, um
India also requested Israeli assistance
to overhaul Prime Minister security
apparatus. So, Israeli specialists were
also consulted for Rajiv Gandhi's
residence as well. So, and and this is
obviously during the period of the the
'85 um I think that period needs to be
looked at is Rajiv Gandhi's role and his
links with Mossad.
And I would I would think Pakistan
intelligence, China probably have way
more information about all this. And
maybe now with John Kiriakou coming out,
there might be some more leaks um and
some more intel particularly since now
people are um
giving Pakistan greater importance uh as
as being a you know, a regional
stabilizer. Because all of India's
actions so far,
you know, if if it can't even keep its
own territory stable, then how is it
going to contribute in being a if
stabilizing force of the region? I think
that's something that needs to be looked
at, too.
Yeah, I just want to and I'll be Yeah, I
appreciate it. Yeah, I just one thing I
want to kind of say before you start. I
want to kind of make sure I make
urge people to follow John Kiriakou. Um
I see follow him follow him on Twitter.
I think this is the least we can do.
Um I see he has a podcast on Apple
called John Kiriakou's Dead Drop. Please
follow him there.
Um
I am talking to certain
>> to say in the last like 6 months it's
hard not to see John. He's gone totally
viral like on every social media. So
Yeah. The timing is Except except he'll
be absent on the Indian media for quite
some time now.
They have been running in
Anyways the we I am trying to work with
certain prominent Sikhs to to actually
honor John, invite him to a Sikh seminar
or something, give him some more
visibility within the bond.
And I also want to urge okay look look
at John. I'm pretty sure there are more
people out there
who know something about this. Please
come up and speak. That's the minimum
you can do.
Nothing's going to happen. This is cat
is out of the bag. It's not going back
in the bag. No Canadian government no
Indian government can stop the truth
from come out. So you better come out
and tell people what you know.
The
What about the families?
I think the families no they have been
following this that what's going on.
They probably have been silenced. I know
they've been made to sign some kind of
NDAs when they were given this
compensation. But maybe they should pick
it up. They should pick it up why John
is alleging it. Canadian government
should clarify. They should issue an
official statement.
The why are they silent? Um the Indian
government no we don't have any
expectation from Indian government like
they they they are kind of the the ones
who did it. But the pressure can be put
on Canadian government like the families
they should take you know the statement
from John and maybe you know ask the
Canadian government give an explanation
um why John is making these statements.
And
yeah so and then if there's anybody else
out there who knows something about it
please talk about it. Please reach out
to people. Please reach out to me. I'm
nobody but I'm happy to share if anybody
had any more information uh about this
Das league attack. Uh,
yeah.
Somebody's
kind of,
uh, clearing his throat, but yeah.
Yeah, he's ready to share something.
Anyways,
Falcon, go ahead.
Yeah, hold on a second. Um, Arjit, I was
going to speak.
Achha, achha, I mean I have to be
natural. I'm sorry about that. Go ahead.
You know, let me speak after that. Don't
mind.
Sure.
I just wanted to say before after the
coins spoke, I just wanted to add
something quickly and then I will go out
of the space because I've got to go to
work, too, so is it okay for you? Okay,
doctor, if you don't mind, let's take
Falcon's turn and then you can
Okay, go ahead, Falcon.
So, as uh, she's spoken the hand of the
Israelis in the in the Operation Blue
Star.
So, as the passenger is saying to you
from Talking About Our Space,
that we as Sikhs, we need to conserve
our energy right now.
So, when the
PLO was there, so I guess that Arafat
traveled to India with his pistol and he
appreciated India and the on that time
the the way he handled the Operation
Blue Star.
And it's on record.
And now, since the Iran war is
happening, and Sikhs are forced, or I
don't know, because of staying with the
Indian regime for too long, our
our brains is also somehow I don't know
and affected.
So, these are two wars where should we
not speak anything.
Because when we were going through the
worst time in the history, no one spoke
for us. No PLO, no Palestinians, no and
even Israelis, they hate us the same.
Because why would they help a third
world country?
So they know that the this kind of a
power Sikhs are. So everyone in the
world will try to stop us.
Even the Britishers,
even the Mughals, whoever. So Sikhs have
to defend themselves right now. This is
the harsh truth. And I hope that I'm not
going out of topic, but it just came
into my mind. So
we vis-a-vis we are alone.
And I think the only true ally we have
right now in the world is United States.
That's all.
So I hope that I wish everyone a nice, I
don't know,
what's the night or day. So I wish you
guys a nice health
and the success in life and
goodbye, guys, huh?
Okay, welcome. Thank you. Thank you for
sharing your thoughts. I will also start
to wrapping up this space, but we'll
have last speakers have their say.
And because I'm going to do more spaces
on this, okay?
John has given us a new fresh life. He
has reminded me that hey, this can't be
let go.
>> the presentation again. Yeah, definitely
multiple times. Yeah, and and you know,
like how like I don't know
whether this was incidental, like
there's a guy who sent me all kind of
video messages to read and I don't
listen to 80% of what he sends me, okay?
And and then but he sent me this video
and I don't obviously I don't listen to
it.
And then he basically called me,
"Harjit, you should listen to this." And
I he's never asked me if I should listen
to this. So what I whatever came in my
mind, I actually started listening to
this interview. And as he said in the
very first minute, I had John saying
this and yeah, I don't know like it was
like a kind of a break in that sense.
But anyways,
Daku ji, go ahead.
Yeah, that's a good point, actually.
Yeah, if John had made the allegations,
yeah, I think what happened was if I
remember correctly,
Dr. G.
A lot of money was paid by Indian
government and Canadian government to
cover up there
to cover up their messes. And uh
I don't know if there was an insurance
company involved.
And but I do know that a good amount of
money was paid by the Indian government
as well as the Canadian government. But,
that's an interesting one if they're
insured.
Yeah, that's a good one. That's a good
one, actually. We should research who
was the insurance company. And maybe
they can sue the Canadian government for
hiding
information that they had about the
Indian
>> compensated more than cuz they were
compensated to remain silent. Yeah.
Maybe we'll see. But, that's an
interesting lead. I'm going to research
on that. Thanks, Dr. G. Okay, I I want
to kind of start wrapping up. I want to
kind of you know, in the end um uh,
want to thank all the John especially
for what he has done.
Uh, you know, my huge respect. Uh, the
pump will remember him. We will also
honor him. I hope I hope, but I also
want to appeal. I want to appeal to the
Indians.
I hope we get one Indian with a sense of
pain.
With a sense of
>> Stephen, can I make one point before you
wrap up completely? Go ahead.
I was going to say that the pattern of
behavior that you may or may not have
noticed or other people may have or may
not have noticed
once the Indian state believes it's
succeeded in a plot, it tries to repeat
it.
They they try to do the same thing over
and over again. So, they did the plot
with the the bombings the of their own
planes.
Then they try and, you know, arrange for
more bombings in Europe.
They don't succeed there. They start to
um,
kill Sikh activists in the UK and
Canada.
They get away with it in these countries
and then they go and try in the US and
they get caught.
Now, I think the US, someone said that
the US is
really the only ones that
um,
will stand,
you know, against India in these kinds
of activities and I I think that's all
we really need is the US.
You know, these other countries are just
a bunch of jokers, to be honest.
The I put a comment in the in the uh,
I put a comment in the space basically
just saying that India, the reason why
these countries aren't going to do
anything against India is because India
is
largely controlled by the city of London
and the financiers and the insurance
companies and those people, so they'll
do their bidding.
That's why you see India's nowhere in
this equation with the Iran
um,
incident
and events that are happening there. You
see Pakistan there.
The countries that have assembled around
the United States at the moment, none of
them are none of them are linked to the
city of London in the way that, you
know, these Commonwealth countries are.
So, that's another thing to keep in in
mind. There's a
There since the Bretton Woods, it's the
city of London that ran the
ran trade and finance around the world
and that's changing. The US doesn't want
that Bretton Woods agreement anymore.
They've had enough of it.
They want
individual countries acting as, you
know, in with their own sovereignty.
And I think part of that's going to end
up in the breakup of India and I think
the US sees that it's a fake country
created for administration and it's a
bad actor
as far as the planet is concerned. So, I
just want to wrap it up there. Thanks.
Yeah, no, absolutely. And um
Yeah, I want to thank everybody for
coming today and you know,
participating. And if people anybody
wants to open a space to continue the
conversation, I would highly
um
There's another person who is just
asking for speaker right now.
But I think we're too late friend Arya.
Um
Um we'll you know, maybe next time. But
yeah, people want to continue the
conversation, you can probably open
another space.
Um I do want to urge everybody to
retweet. I have made certain tweet
threads on this on John's revelation.
Please retweet it as much as you can. If
you have any links, any relatives in
media, in Punjabi media, in English
media, please try to make a case with
them that they should at least talk
about John's revelations. Um
please
at the minimum RT it RT it multiple
times.
I'll try to do my best to do more spaces
on this.
But I think whatever we can do to to to
get truth out I think that that helps.
And so that's my request. Hope everybody
can do their bit. You've already done a
lot by coming here spending so much time
talking about this. But let's keep
talking about Air India 182 until the
Canadian government does not tell us
what they already know.
Thank you so much everybody. Waheguru Ji
Ka Khalsa. Waheguru Ji Ki Fateh.